From",0,O,0
55,this,DT,.,.,O,0.903,"O
From",0
56,climate,NN,DT,this,O,0.222,O,0
57,William,NNP,NN,climate,I-PER,0.976,O,1
58,Godwin,NNP,NNP,William,I-PER,0.416,I-PER,1
59,developed,VBD,NNP,Godwin,O,0.299,I-PER,0
60,what,WP,VBD,developed,O,0.969,O,0
61,many,NN,WP,what,O,0.56,O,0
62,consider,VBP,NN,many,O,0.245,O,0
63,the,DT,VBP,consider,O,0.895,O,0
64,first,JJ,DT,the,O,0.383,O,0
65,expression,NN,JJ,first,O,0.364,O,0
66,of,IN,NN,expression,O,0.639,O,0
67,modern,JJ,IN,of,O,0.594,O,0
68,anarchist,NN,JJ,modern,O,0.101,O,0
69,thought,NN,NN,anarchist,O,0.906,O,0
70,.,.,NN,thought,"O
Godwin",0,O,0
71,was,VBD,.,.,O,0.96,"O
Godwin",0
72,",",",",VBD,was,O,0,O,0
73,according,VBG,",",",",O,0.058,O,0
74,to,TO,VBG,according,O,0.911,O,0
75,Peter,NNP,TO,to,I-PER,0.683,O,1
76,Kropotkin,NNP,NNP,Peter,I-PER,0.518,I-PER,1
77,",",",",NNP,Kropotkin,O,0,I-PER,0
78,"""",LQU,",",",",O,0,O,0
79,the,DT,LQU,"""",O,0.895,O,0
80,first,JJ,DT,the,O,0.383,O,0
81,to,TO,JJ,first,O,0.911,O,0
82,formulate,VB,TO,to,O,0.393,O,0
83,the,DT,VB,formulate,O,0.895,O,0
84,political,JJ,DT,the,O,0.696,O,0
85,and,CC,JJ,political,O,0.104,O,0
86,economical,JJ,CC,and,O,0.323,O,0
87,conceptions,NNS,JJ,economical,O,0.239,O,0
88,of,IN,NNS,conceptions,O,0.639,O,0
89,anarchism,NN,IN,of,O,0.101,O,0
90,",",",",NN,anarchism,O,0,O,0
91,even,RB,",",",",O,0.351,O,0
92,though,IN,RB,even,O,0.905,O,0
93,he,PRP,IN,though,O,0.438,O,0
94,did,VBD,PRP,he,O,0.302,O,0
95,not,RB,VBD,did,O,0.629,O,0
96,give,VB,RB,not,O,0.414,O,0
97,that,DT,VB,give,O,0.894,O,0
98,name,NN,DT,that,O,0.61,O,0
99,to,TO,NN,name,O,0.911,O,0
100,the,DT,TO,to,O,0.895,O,0
101,ideas,NNS,DT,the,O,0.466,O,0
102,developed,VBN,NNS,ideas,O,0.299,O,0
103,in,IN,VBN,developed,O,0.472,O,0
104,his,PRP$,IN,in,O,0.453,O,0
105,work,NN,PRP$,his,O,0.987,O,0
106,"""",RQU,NN,work,O,0,O,0
107,",",",",RQU,"""",O,0,O,0
108,while,IN,",",",",O,0.972,O,0
109,Godwin,NNP,IN,while,I-PER,0.416,O,1
110,attached,VBD,NNP,Godwin,O,0.125,I-PER,0
111,his,PRP$,VBD,attached,O,0.453,O,0
112,anarchist,NN,PRP$,his,O,0.101,O,0
113,ideas,NNS,NN,anarchist,O,0.466,O,0
114,to,TO,NNS,ideas,O,0.911,O,0
115,an,DT,TO,to,O,0.1,O,0
116,early,JJ,DT,an,O,0.32,O,0
117,Edmund,NNP,JJ,early,I-PER,0.324,O,1
118,Burke,NNP,NNP,Edmund,I-PER,0.182,I-PER,1
119,.,.,NNP,Burke,"O
Its",0,I-PER,0
120,classical,JJ,.,.,O,0.22,"O
Its",0
121,period,NN,JJ,classical,O,0.679,O,0
122,",",",",NN,period,O,0,O,0
123,which,WDT,",",",",O,0.972,O,0
124,scholars,NNS,WDT,which,O,0.805,O,0
125,demarcate,VBP,NNS,scholars,O,0.291,O,0
126,as,IN,VBP,demarcate,O,0.12,O,0
127,from,IN,IN,as,O,0.403,O,0
128,1860,CD,IN,from,O,0.011,O,0
129,to,TO,CD,1860,O,0.911,O,0
130,1939,CD,TO,to,O,0.019,O,0
131,",",",",CD,1939,O,0,O,0
132,is,VBZ,",",",",O,0.502,O,0
133,associated,VBN,VBZ,is,O,0.123,O,0
134,with,IN,VBN,associated,O,0.98,O,0
135,the,DT,IN,with,O,0.895,O,0
136,working-class,JJ,DT,the,O,0,O,0
137,movements,NNS,JJ,working-class,O,0.606,O,0
138,of,IN,NNS,movements,O,0.639,O,0
139,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
140,nineteenth,JJ,DT,the,O,0.624,O,0
141,century,NN,JJ,nineteenth,O,0.204,O,0
142,and,CC,NN,century,O,0.104,O,0
143,the,DT,CC,and,O,0.895,O,0
144,Spanish,NNP,DT,the,I-MISC,0.849,O,1
145,Civil,NNP,NNP,Spanish,I-MISC,0.218,I-MISC,1
146,War-era,NNP,NNP,Civil,I-MISC,0,I-MISC,1
147,struggles,VBZ,NNP,War-era,O,0.869,I-MISC,0
148,against,IN,VBZ,struggles,O,0.077,O,0
149,fascism,NN,IN,against,O,0.37,O,0
150,.,.,NN,fascism,"O
Karl",0,O,0
167,Marx,NNP,.,.,I-PER,0.565,"O
Karl",1
168,became,VBD,NNP,Marx,O,0.145,I-PER,0
169,a,DT,VBD,became,O,0,O,0
170,leading,JJ,DT,a,O,0.53,O,0
171,figure,NN,JJ,leading,O,0.379,O,0
172,in,IN,NN,figure,O,0.472,O,0
173,the,DT,IN,in,I-MISC,0.895,O,0
174,International,NNP,DT,the,I-MISC,0.494,I-MISC,1
175,and,CC,NNP,International,O,0.104,I-MISC,0
176,a,DT,CC,and,O,0,O,0
177,member,NN,DT,a,O,0.574,O,0
178,of,IN,NN,member,O,0.639,O,0
179,its,PRP$,IN,of,O,0.504,O,0
180,General,NNP,PRP$,its,I-ORG,0.409,O,1
181,Council,NNP,NNP,General,I-ORG,0.261,I-ORG,1
182,.,.,NNP,Council,"O
Proudhon",0,I-ORG,0
183,'s,POS,.,.,O,0,"O
Proudhon",0
184,followers,NNS,POS,'s,O,0.387,O,0
185,",",",",NNS,followers,O,0,O,0
186,the,DT,",",",",O,0.895,O,0
187,mutualists,NNS,DT,the,O,0.608,O,0
188,",",",",NNS,mutualists,O,0,O,0
189,opposed,VBD,",",",",O,0.649,O,0
190,Marx,NNP,VBD,opposed,I-PER,0.565,O,1
191,'s,POS,NNP,Marx,O,0,I-PER,0
192,state,NN,POS,'s,O,0.857,O,0
193,socialism,NN,NN,state,O,0.838,O,0
194,",",",",NN,socialism,O,0,O,0
195,advocating,VBG,",",",",O,0.074,O,0
196,political,JJ,VBG,advocating,O,0.696,O,0
197,abstentionism,NN,JJ,political,O,0.057,O,0
198,and,CC,NN,abstentionism,O,0.104,O,0
199,small,JJ,CC,and,O,0.835,O,0
200,property,NN,JJ,small,O,0.725,O,0
201,holdings,NNS,NN,property,O,0.456,O,0
202,.,.,NNS,holdings,"O
They",0,O,0
203,allied,VBD,.,.,O,0.089,"O
They",0
204,themselves,PRP,VBD,allied,O,0.897,O,0
205,with,IN,PRP,themselves,O,0.98,O,0
206,the,DT,IN,with,O,0.895,O,0
207,federalist,JJ,DT,the,O,0.373,O,0
208,socialist,JJ,JJ,federalist,O,0.838,O,0
209,sections,NNS,JJ,socialist,O,0.812,O,0
210,of,IN,NNS,sections,O,0.639,O,0
211,the,DT,IN,of,I-MISC,0.895,O,0
212,International,NNP,DT,the,I-MISC,0.494,I-MISC,1
213,",",",",NNP,International,O,0,I-MISC,0
214,who,WP,",",",",O,0.974,O,0
215,advocated,VBD,WP,who,O,0.072,O,0
216,the,DT,VBD,advocated,O,0.895,O,0
217,revolutionary,JJ,DT,the,O,0.785,O,0
218,overthrow,NN,JJ,revolutionary,O,0.661,O,0
219,of,IN,NN,overthrow,O,0.639,O,0
220,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
221,state,NN,DT,the,O,0.857,O,0
222,and,CC,NN,state,O,0.104,O,0
223,the,DT,CC,and,O,0.895,O,0
224,collectivization,NN,DT,the,O,0.226,O,0
225,of,IN,NN,collectivization,O,0.639,O,0
226,property,NN,IN,of,O,0.725,O,0
227,.,.,NN,property,"O
Subsequently",0,O,0
228,",",",",.,.,O,0,"O
Subsequently",0
229,the,DT,",",",",I-MISC,0.895,O,0
230,International,NNP,DT,the,I-MISC,0.494,I-MISC,1
231,became,VBD,NNP,International,O,0.145,I-MISC,0
232,polarised,VBN,VBD,became,O,0.695,O,0
233,into,IN,VBN,polarised,O,0.497,O,0
234,two,CD,IN,into,O,0.929,O,0
235,camps,NNS,CD,two,O,0.189,O,0
236,",",",",NNS,camps,O,0,O,0
237,with,IN,",",",",O,0.98,O,0
238,Marx,NNP,IN,with,I-PER,0.565,O,1
239,and,CC,NNP,Marx,O,0.104,I-PER,0
240,Bakunin,NNP,CC,and,I-PER,0.134,O,1
241,as,IN,NNP,Bakunin,O,0.12,I-PER,0
242,their,PRP$,IN,as,O,0.896,O,0
243,respective,JJ,PRP$,their,O,0.775,O,0
244,figureheads,NNS,JJ,respective,O,0.38,O,0
245,.,.,NNS,figureheads,"O
In",0,O,0
246,response,NN,.,.,O,0.777,"O
In",0
247,",",",",NN,response,O,0,O,0
248,unions,NNS,",",",",O,0.933,O,0
249,across,IN,NNS,unions,O,0.063,O,0
250,America,NNP,IN,across,I-LOC,0.095,O,1
251,prepared,VBD,NNP,America,O,0.711,I-LOC,0
252,a,DT,VBD,prepared,O,0,O,0
253,general,JJ,DT,a,O,0.409,O,0
254,strike,NN,JJ,general,O,0.864,O,0
255,in,IN,NN,strike,O,0.472,O,0
256,support,NN,IN,in,O,0.877,O,0
257,of,IN,NN,support,O,0.639,O,0
258,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
259,event,NN,DT,the,O,0.352,O,0
260,.,.,NN,event,"O
The",0,O,0
261,incident,NN,.,.,O,0.473,"O
The",0
262,became,VBD,NN,incident,O,0.145,O,0
263,known,VBN,VBD,became,O,0.517,O,0
264,as,IN,VBN,known,O,0.12,O,0
265,the,DT,IN,as,O,0.895,O,0
266,Haymarket,NNP,DT,the,I-PER,0.438,O,1
267,affair,NN,NNP,Haymarket,I-PER,0.075,I-PER,0
268,",",",",NN,affair,O,0,I-PER,0
269,and,CC,",",",",O,0.104,O,0
270,was,VBD,CC,and,O,0.96,O,0
271,a,DT,VBD,was,O,0,O,0
272,setback,NN,DT,a,O,0.818,O,0
273,for,IN,NN,setback,O,0.389,O,0
274,the,DT,IN,for,O,0.895,O,0
275,labour,NN,DT,the,O,0.521,O,0
276,movement,NN,NN,labour,O,0.605,O,0
277,and,CC,NN,movement,O,0.104,O,0
278,the,DT,CC,and,O,0.895,O,0
279,struggle,NN,DT,the,O,0.869,O,0
280,for,IN,NN,struggle,O,0.389,O,0
281,the,DT,IN,for,O,0.895,O,0
282,eight,CD,DT,the,O,0.332,O,0
283,hour,NN,CD,eight,O,0.46,O,0
284,day,NN,NN,hour,O,0.279,O,0
285,.,.,NN,day,"O
The",0,O,0
286,event,NN,.,.,O,0.352,"O
The",0
287,also,RB,NN,event,O,0.092,O,0
288,had,VBD,RB,also,O,0.431,O,0
289,the,DT,VBD,had,O,0.895,O,0
290,secondary,JJ,DT,the,O,0.811,O,0
291,purpose,NN,JJ,secondary,O,0.737,O,0
292,of,IN,NN,purpose,O,0.639,O,0
293,memorializing,VBG,IN,of,O,0.576,O,0
294,workers,NNS,VBG,memorializing,O,0.987,O,0
295,killed,VBN,NNS,workers,O,0.515,O,0
296,as,IN,VBN,killed,O,0.12,O,0
297,a,DT,IN,as,O,0,O,0
298,result,NN,DT,a,O,0.778,O,0
299,of,IN,NN,result,O,0.639,O,0
300,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
301,Haymarket,NNP,DT,the,I-PER,0.438,O,1
302,affair,NN,NNP,Haymarket,I-PER,0.075,I-PER,0
303,.,.,NN,affair,"O
The",0,O,0
337,most,RBS,.,.,O,0.599,"O
The",0
338,successful,JJ,RBS,most,O,0.872,O,0
339,was,VBD,JJ,successful,O,0.96,O,0
340,the,DT,VBD,was,O,0.895,O,0
341,Confederación,NNP,DT,the,I-ORG,0.24,O,1
342,Nacional,NNP,NNP,Confederación,I-ORG,0.61,I-ORG,1
343,del,NNP,NNP,Nacional,I-ORG,0.29,I-ORG,0
344,Trabajo,NNP,NNP,del,I-ORG,0.915,I-ORG,1
345,(,LRB,NNP,Trabajo,O,0,I-ORG,0
346,National,NNP,LRB,(,I-ORG,0.614,O,1
347,Confederation,NNP,NNP,National,I-ORG,0.241,I-ORG,1
348,of,IN,NNP,Confederation,I-ORG,0.639,I-ORG,0
349,Labour,NNP,IN,of,I-ORG,0.521,I-ORG,1
350,:,IN,NNP,Labour,O,0,I-ORG,0
351,CNT,NNP,IN,:,I-ORG,0.223,O,3
352,),RRB,NNP,CNT,O,0,I-ORG,0
353,",",",",RRB,),O,0,O,0
354,founded,VBN,",",",",O,0.396,O,0
355,in,IN,VBN,founded,O,0.472,O,0
356,1910,CD,IN,in,O,0.013,O,0
357,.,.,CD,1910,"O
CGT",0,O,0
358,membership,NN,.,.,O,0.575,"O
CGT",0
359,was,VBD,NN,membership,O,0.96,O,0
360,estimated,VBN,VBD,was,O,0.35,O,0
361,to,TO,VBN,estimated,O,0.911,O,0
362,be,VB,TO,to,O,0.143,O,0
363,around,IN,VB,be,O,0.119,O,0
364,"100,000",CD,IN,around,O,0,O,0
365,for,IN,CD,"100,000",O,0.389,O,0
366,the,DT,IN,for,O,0.895,O,0
367,year,NN,DT,the,O,0.995,O,0
368,2003,CD,NN,year,O,0.027,O,0
369,.,.,CD,2003,"O
Other",0,O,0
370,active,JJ,.,.,O,0.066,"O
Other",0
371,syndicalist,NN,JJ,active,O,0.88,O,0
372,movements,NNS,NN,syndicalist,O,0.606,O,0
373,include,VBP,NNS,movements,O,0.473,O,0
374,the,DT,VBP,include,O,0.895,O,0
375,US,NNP,DT,the,I-LOC,0.938,O,3
376,Workers,NNPS,NNP,US,I-ORG,0.987,I-LOC,1
377,Solidarity,NNP,NNPS,Workers,I-ORG,0.841,I-ORG,1
378,Alliance,NNP,NNP,Solidarity,I-ORG,0.088,I-ORG,1
379,and,CC,NNP,Alliance,O,0.104,I-ORG,0
380,the,DT,CC,and,O,0.895,O,0
381,UK,NNP,DT,the,I-LOC,0.931,O,3
382,Solidarity,NNP,NNP,UK,I-ORG,0.841,I-LOC,1
383,Federation,NNP,NNP,Solidarity,I-ORG,0.373,I-ORG,1
384,.,.,NNP,Federation,"O
Some",0,I-ORG,0
385,anarchists,NNS,.,.,O,0.102,"O
Some",0
386,",",",",NNS,anarchists,O,0,O,0
387,such,JJ,",",",",O,0.872,O,0
388,as,IN,JJ,such,O,0.12,O,0
389,Johann,NNP,IN,as,I-PER,0.508,O,1
390,Most,NNP,NNP,Johann,I-PER,0.599,I-PER,1
391,",",",",NNP,Most,O,0,I-PER,0
392,advocated,VBD,",",",",O,0.072,O,0
393,publicizing,VBG,VBD,advocated,O,0.735,O,0
394,violent,JJ,VBG,publicizing,O,0.949,O,0
395,acts,NNS,JJ,violent,O,0.068,O,0
396,of,IN,NNS,acts,O,0.639,O,0
397,retaliation,NN,IN,of,O,0.78,O,0
398,against,IN,NN,retaliation,O,0.077,O,0
399,counter-revolutionaries,NNS,IN,against,O,0,O,0
400,because,IN,NNS,counter-revolutionaries,O,0.146,O,0
401,"""",LQU,IN,because,O,0,O,0
402,we,PRP,LQU,"""",O,0.961,O,0
403,preach,VBP,PRP,we,O,0.709,O,0
404,not,RB,VBP,preach,O,0.629,O,0
405,only,RB,RB,not,O,0.645,O,0
406,action,NN,RB,only,O,0.065,O,0
407,in,IN,NN,action,O,0.472,O,0
408,and,CC,IN,in,O,0.104,O,0
409,for,IN,CC,and,O,0.389,O,0
410,itself,PRP,IN,for,O,0.505,O,0
411,",",",",PRP,itself,O,0,O,0
412,but,CC,",",",",O,0.185,O,0
413,also,RB,CC,but,O,0.092,O,0
414,action,NN,RB,also,O,0.065,O,0
415,as,IN,NN,action,O,0.12,O,0
416,propaganda,NN,IN,as,O,0.724,O,0
417,.,.,NN,propaganda,O,0,O,0
418,"""",RQU,.,.,"O
The",0,O,0
419,anarcho-syndicalist,NN,RQU,"""",O,0,"O
The",0
420,",",",",NN,anarcho-syndicalist,O,0,O,0
421,Fernand,NNP,",",",",I-PER,0.376,O,1
422,Pelloutier,NNP,NNP,Fernand,I-PER,0.676,I-PER,1
423,",",",",NNP,Pelloutier,O,0,I-PER,0
424,argued,VBD,",",",",O,0.117,O,0
425,in,IN,VBD,argued,O,0.472,O,0
426,1895,CD,IN,in,O,0.012,O,0
427,for,IN,CD,1895,O,0.389,O,0
428,renewed,VBN,IN,for,O,0.767,O,0
429,anarchist,NN,VBN,renewed,O,0.101,O,0
430,involvement,NN,NN,anarchist,O,0.499,O,0
431,in,IN,NN,involvement,O,0.472,O,0
432,the,DT,IN,in,O,0.895,O,0
433,labor,NN,DT,the,O,0.52,O,0
434,movement,NN,NN,labor,O,0.605,O,0
435,on,IN,NN,movement,O,0.644,O,0
436,the,DT,IN,on,O,0.895,O,0
437,basis,NN,DT,the,O,0.14,O,0
438,that,IN,NN,basis,O,0.894,O,0
439,anarchism,NN,IN,that,O,0.101,O,0
440,could,MD,NN,anarchism,O,0.26,O,0
441,do,VB,MD,could,O,0.311,O,0
442,very,RB,VB,do,O,0.945,O,0
443,well,RB,RB,very,O,0.966,O,0
444,without,IN,RB,well,O,0.982,O,0
445,"""",LQU,IN,without,O,0,O,0
446,the,DT,LQU,"""",O,0.895,O,0
447,individual,JJ,DT,the,O,0.478,O,0
448,dynamiter,NN,JJ,individual,O,0.318,O,0
449,.,.,NN,dynamiter,O,0,O,0
This",0,I-PER,0
472,was,VBD,.,.,O,0.96,"O
This",0
473,in,IN,VBD,was,O,0.472,O,0
474,spite,NN,IN,in,O,0.852,O,0
475,of,IN,NN,spite,O,0.639,O,0
476,Goldman,NNP,IN,of,I-PER,0.417,O,1
477,'s,POS,NNP,Goldman,O,0,I-PER,0
478,disavowal,NN,POS,'s,O,0.305,O,0
479,of,IN,NN,disavowal,O,0.639,O,0
480,any,DT,IN,of,O,0.11,O,0
481,association,NN,DT,any,O,0.124,O,0
482,with,IN,NN,association,O,0.98,O,0
483,him,PRP,IN,with,O,0.452,O,0
484,",",",",PRP,him,O,0,O,0
485,his,PRP$,",",",",O,0.453,O,0
486,registered,JJ,PRP$,his,O,0.762,O,0
487,membership,NN,JJ,registered,O,0.575,O,0
488,in,IN,NN,membership,O,0.472,O,0
489,the,DT,IN,in,O,0.895,O,0
490,Republican,NNP,DT,the,I-ORG,0.771,O,1
491,Party,NNP,NNP,Republican,I-ORG,0.671,I-ORG,1
492,",",",",NNP,Party,O,0,I-ORG,0
493,and,CC,",",",",O,0.104,O,0
494,never,RB,CC,and,O,0.62,O,0
495,having,VBG,RB,never,O,0.437,O,0
496,belonged,VBN,VBG,having,O,0.154,O,0
497,to,TO,VBN,belonged,O,0.911,O,0
498,an,DT,TO,to,O,0.1,O,0
499,anarchist,NN,DT,an,O,0.101,O,0
500,organization,NN,NN,anarchist,O,0.653,O,0
501,.,.,NN,organization,"O
Propaganda",0,O,0
502,of,IN,.,.,O,0.639,"O
Propaganda",0
503,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
504,deed,NN,DT,the,O,0.287,O,0
505,was,VBD,NN,deed,O,0.96,O,0
506,abandoned,VBN,VBD,was,O,0.055,O,0
507,by,IN,VBN,abandoned,O,0.185,O,0
508,the,DT,IN,by,O,0.895,O,0
509,vast,JJ,DT,the,O,0.942,O,0
510,majority,NN,JJ,vast,O,0.557,O,0
511,of,IN,NN,majority,O,0.639,O,0
512,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
513,anarchist,NN,DT,the,O,0.101,O,0
514,movement,NN,NN,anarchist,O,0.605,O,0
515,after,IN,NN,movement,O,0.076,O,0
516,World,NNP,IN,after,I-MISC,0.989,O,1
517,War,NNP,NNP,World,I-MISC,0.957,I-MISC,1
518,I,NNP,NNP,War,I-MISC,0,I-MISC,3
519,(,LRB,NNP,I,O,0,I-MISC,0
520,1914,CD,LRB,(,O,0.014,O,0
521,--,:,CD,1914,O,0,O,0
522,18,CD,:,--,O,0.007,O,0
523,),RRB,CD,18,O,0,O,0
524,and,CC,RRB,),O,0.104,O,0
525,the,DT,CC,and,O,0.895,O,0
526,1917,CD,DT,the,I-MISC,0.015,O,0
527,October,NNP,CD,1917,I-MISC,0.638,I-MISC,1
528,Revolution,NN,NNP,October,I-MISC,0.784,I-MISC,1
529,.,.,NN,Revolution,"O
Anarchists",0,O,0
558,participated,VBD,.,.,O,0.669,"O
Anarchists",0
559,alongside,IN,VBD,participated,O,0.092,O,0
560,the,DT,IN,alongside,O,0.895,O,0
561,Bolsheviks,NNS,DT,the,I-ORG,0.168,O,1
562,in,IN,NNS,Bolsheviks,O,0.472,I-ORG,0
563,both,DT,IN,in,O,0.171,O,0
564,February,NNP,DT,both,O,0.372,O,1
565,and,CC,NNP,February,O,0.104,O,0
566,October,NNP,CC,and,I-MISC,0.638,O,1
567,revolutions,NNS,NNP,October,I-MISC,0.786,I-MISC,0
568,",",",",NNS,revolutions,O,0,I-MISC,0
569,and,CC,",",",",O,0.104,O,0
570,were,VBD,CC,and,O,0.967,O,0
571,initially,RB,VBD,were,O,0.487,O,0
572,enthusiastic,JJ,RB,initially,O,0.344,O,0
573,about,IN,JJ,enthusiastic,O,0.056,O,0
574,the,DT,IN,about,O,0.895,O,0
575,Bolshevik,NNP,DT,the,I-ORG,0.168,O,1
576,coup,NN,NNP,Bolshevik,O,0.264,I-ORG,0
577,.,.,NN,coup,"O
However",0,O,0
578,",",",",.,.,O,0,"O
However",0
579,the,DT,",",",",O,0.895,O,0
580,Bolsheviks,NNP,DT,the,I-ORG,0.168,O,1
581,soon,RB,NNP,Bolsheviks,O,0.843,I-ORG,0
582,turned,VBD,RB,soon,O,0.927,O,0
583,against,IN,VBD,turned,O,0.077,O,0
584,the,DT,IN,against,O,0.895,O,0
585,anarchists,NNS,DT,the,O,0.102,O,0
586,and,CC,NNS,anarchists,O,0.104,O,0
587,other,JJ,CC,and,O,0.654,O,0
588,left-wing,JJ,JJ,other,O,0,O,0
589,opposition,NN,JJ,left-wing,O,0.65,O,0
590,",",",",NN,opposition,O,0,O,0
591,a,DT,",",",",O,0,O,0
592,conflict,NN,DT,a,O,0.242,O,0
593,that,WDT,NN,conflict,O,0.894,O,0
594,culminated,VBD,WDT,that,O,0.271,O,0
595,in,IN,VBD,culminated,O,0.472,O,0
596,the,DT,IN,in,O,0.895,O,0
597,1921,CD,DT,the,O,0.017,O,0
598,Kronstadt,NNP,CD,1921,I-MISC,0.517,O,1
599,rebellion,NN,NNP,Kronstadt,I-MISC,0.749,I-MISC,0
600,which,WDT,NN,rebellion,O,0.972,I-MISC,0
601,the,DT,WDT,which,O,0.895,O,0
602,new,JJ,DT,the,O,0.621,O,0
603,government,NN,JJ,new,O,0.419,O,0
604,repressed,VBD,NN,government,O,0.77,O,0
605,.,.,VBD,repressed,"O
Both",0,O,0
606,wrote,VBD,.,.,O,0.993,"O
Both",0
607,accounts,NNS,VBD,wrote,O,0.059,O,0
608,of,IN,NNS,accounts,O,0.639,O,0
609,their,PRP$,IN,of,O,0.896,O,0
610,experiences,NNS,PRP$,their,O,0.361,O,0
611,in,IN,NNS,experiences,O,0.472,O,0
612,Russia,NNP,IN,in,I-LOC,0.799,O,1
613,",",",",NNP,Russia,O,0,I-LOC,0
614,criticizing,VBG,",",",",O,0.27,O,0
615,the,DT,VBG,criticizing,O,0.895,O,0
616,amount,NN,DT,the,O,0.098,O,0
617,of,IN,NN,amount,O,0.639,O,0
618,control,NN,IN,of,O,0.252,O,0
619,the,DT,NN,control,O,0.895,O,0
620,Bolsheviks,NNPS,DT,the,I-ORG,0.168,O,1
621,exercised,VBD,NNPS,Bolsheviks,O,0.358,I-ORG,0
622,.,.,VBD,exercised,"O
The",0,O,0
623,victory,NN,.,.,O,0.946,"O
The",0
624,of,IN,NN,victory,O,0.639,O,0
625,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
626,Bolsheviks,NNS,DT,the,I-ORG,0.168,O,1
627,in,IN,NNS,Bolsheviks,O,0.472,I-ORG,0
628,the,DT,IN,in,O,0.895,O,0
629,October,NNP,DT,the,I-MISC,0.638,O,1
630,Revolution,NN,NNP,October,I-MISC,0.784,I-MISC,1
631,and,CC,NN,Revolution,O,0.104,I-MISC,0
632,the,DT,CC,and,O,0.895,O,0
633,resulting,VBG,DT,the,O,0.779,O,0
634,Russian,NNP,VBG,resulting,I-MISC,0.8,O,1
635,Civil,NNP,NNP,Russian,I-MISC,0.218,I-MISC,1
636,War,NNP,NNP,Civil,I-MISC,0.957,I-MISC,1
637,did,VBD,NNP,War,O,0.302,I-MISC,0
638,serious,JJ,VBD,did,O,0.816,O,0
639,damage,NN,JJ,serious,O,0.276,O,0
640,to,TO,NN,damage,O,0.911,O,0
641,anarchist,NN,TO,to,O,0.101,O,0
642,movements,NNS,NN,anarchist,O,0.606,O,0
643,internationally,RB,NNS,movements,O,0.495,O,0
644,.,.,RB,internationally,"O
Italian",0,O,0
645,anarchists,NNS,.,.,I-ORG,0.102,"O
Italian",0
646,played,VBD,NNS,anarchists,O,0.692,I-ORG,0
647,a,DT,VBD,played,O,0,O,0
648,key,JJ,DT,a,O,0.514,O,0
649,role,NN,JJ,key,O,0.793,O,0
650,in,IN,NN,role,O,0.472,O,0
651,the,DT,IN,in,O,0.895,O,0
652,anti-fascist,JJ,DT,the,O,0,O,0
653,organisation,NN,JJ,anti-fascist,O,0.653,O,0
654,Arditi,NNP,NN,organisation,I-MISC,0.114,O,1
655,del,NNP,NNP,Arditi,I-MISC,0.29,I-MISC,0
656,Popolo,NNP,NNP,del,I-MISC,0.698,I-MISC,1
657,",",",",NNP,Popolo,O,0,I-MISC,0
658,which,WDT,",",",",O,0.972,O,0
659,was,VBD,WDT,which,O,0.96,O,0
660,strongest,JJS,VBD,was,O,0.866,O,0
661,in,IN,JJS,strongest,O,0.472,O,0
662,areas,NNS,IN,in,O,0.116,O,0
663,with,IN,NNS,areas,O,0.98,O,0
664,anarchist,JJ,IN,with,O,0.101,O,0
665,traditions,NNS,JJ,anarchist,O,0.917,O,0
666,",",",",NNS,traditions,O,0,O,0
667,and,CC,",",",",O,0.104,O,0
668,achieved,VBD,CC,and,O,0.06,O,0
669,some,DT,VBD,achieved,O,0.841,O,0
670,success,NN,DT,some,O,0.871,O,0
671,in,IN,NN,success,O,0.472,O,0
672,their,PRP$,IN,in,O,0.896,O,0
673,activism,NN,PRP$,their,O,0.066,O,0
674,",",",",NN,activism,O,0,O,0
675,such,JJ,",",",",O,0.872,O,0
676,as,IN,JJ,such,O,0.12,O,0
677,repelling,VBG,IN,as,O,0.768,O,0
678,Blackshirts,NNS,VBG,repelling,I-ORG,0.163,O,1
679,in,IN,NNS,Blackshirts,O,0.472,I-ORG,0
680,the,DT,IN,in,O,0.895,O,0
681,anarchist,NN,DT,the,O,0.101,O,0
682,stronghold,NN,NN,anarchist,O,0.867,O,0
683,of,IN,NN,stronghold,O,0.639,O,0
684,Parma,NNP,IN,of,I-LOC,0.667,O,1
685,in,IN,NNP,Parma,O,0.472,I-LOC,0
686,August,NNP,IN,in,O,0.129,O,1
687,1922,CD,NNP,August,O,0.017,O,0
688,.,.,CD,1922,"O
But",0,O,0
689,in,IN,.,.,O,0.472,"O
But",0
690,1936,CD,IN,in,O,0.018,O,0
691,",",",",CD,1936,O,0,O,0
692,the,DT,",",",",O,0.895,O,0
693,CNT,NNP,DT,the,I-ORG,0.223,O,3
694,changed,VBD,NNP,CNT,O,0.206,I-ORG,0
695,its,PRP$,VBD,changed,O,0.504,O,0
696,policy,NN,PRP$,its,O,0.695,O,0
697,and,CC,NN,policy,O,0.104,O,0
698,anarchist,NN,CC,and,O,0.101,O,0
699,votes,NNS,NN,anarchist,O,0.952,O,0
700,helped,VBD,NNS,votes,O,0.445,O,0
701,bring,VB,VBD,helped,O,0.175,O,0
702,the,DT,VB,bring,O,0.895,O,0
703,popular,JJ,DT,the,O,0.699,O,0
704,front,NN,JJ,popular,O,0.403,O,0
705,back,RB,NN,front,O,0.133,O,0
706,to,TO,RB,back,O,0.911,O,0
707,power,NN,TO,to,O,0.706,O,0
708,.,.,NN,power,"O
Months",0,O,0
709,later,RB,.,.,O,0.528,"O
Months",0
710,",",",",RB,later,O,0,O,0
711,the,DT,",",",",O,0.895,O,0
712,former,JJ,DT,the,O,0.393,O,0
713,ruling,NN,JJ,former,O,0.796,O,0
714,class,NN,NN,ruling,O,0.22,O,0
715,responded,VBD,NN,class,O,0.776,O,0
716,with,IN,VBD,responded,O,0.98,O,0
717,an,DT,IN,with,O,0.1,O,0
718,attempted,VBN,DT,an,O,0.126,O,0
719,coup,NN,VBN,attempted,O,0.264,O,0
720,causing,VBG,NN,coup,O,0.199,O,0
721,the,DT,VBG,causing,O,0.895,O,0
722,Spanish,JJ,DT,the,I-MISC,0.849,O,1
723,Civil,NNP,JJ,Spanish,I-MISC,0.218,I-MISC,1
724,War,NNP,NNP,Civil,I-MISC,0.957,I-MISC,1
725,(,LRB,NNP,War,O,0,I-MISC,0
726,1936,CD,LRB,(,O,0.018,O,0
727,--,:,CD,1936,O,0,O,0
728,1939,CD,:,--,O,0.019,O,0
729,),RRB,CD,1939,O,0,O,0
730,.,.,RRB,),"O
In",0,O,0
743,the,DT,.,.,O,0.895,"O
In",0
744,U.K.,NNP,DT,the,I-LOC,0,O,2
745,this,DT,NNP,U.K.,O,0.903,I-LOC,0
746,was,VBD,DT,this,O,0.96,O,0
747,associated,VBN,VBD,was,O,0.123,O,0
748,with,IN,VBN,associated,O,0.98,O,0
749,the,DT,IN,with,O,0.895,O,0
750,punk,NN,DT,the,O,0.736,O,0
751,rock,NN,NN,punk,O,0.792,O,0
752,movement,NN,NN,rock,O,0.605,O,0
753,",",",",NN,movement,O,0,O,0
754,as,IN,",",",",O,0.12,O,0
755,exemplified,VBN,IN,as,O,0.358,O,0
756,by,IN,VBN,exemplified,O,0.185,O,0
757,bands,NNS,IN,by,O,0.136,O,0
758,such,JJ,NNS,bands,O,0.872,O,0
759,as,IN,JJ,such,O,0.12,O,0
760,Crass,NNP,IN,as,I-ORG,0.265,O,1
761,and,CC,NNP,Crass,O,0.104,I-ORG,0
762,the,DT,CC,and,O,0.895,O,0
763,Sex,NN,DT,the,I-ORG,0.821,O,1
764,Pistols,NNS,NN,Sex,I-ORG,0.687,I-ORG,1
765,.,.,NNS,Pistols,"O
Anarchist",0,I-ORG,0
766,anthropologist,NN,.,.,O,0.109,"O
Anarchist",0
767,David,NNP,NN,anthropologist,I-PER,0.278,O,1
768,Graeber,NNP,NNP,David,I-PER,0.422,I-PER,1
769,and,CC,NNP,Graeber,O,0.104,I-PER,0
770,anarchist,JJ,CC,and,O,0.101,O,0
771,historian,NN,JJ,anarchist,O,0.454,O,0
772,Andrej,NNP,NN,historian,I-PER,0.105,O,1
773,Grubacic,NNP,NNP,Andrej,I-PER,0.428,I-PER,1
774,have,VBP,NNP,Grubacic,O,0.437,I-PER,0
775,posited,VBN,VBP,have,O,0.701,O,0
776,a,DT,VBN,posited,O,0,O,0
777,rupture,NN,DT,a,O,0.797,O,0
778,between,IN,NN,rupture,O,0.157,O,0
779,generations,NNS,IN,between,O,0.41,O,0
780,of,IN,NNS,generations,O,0.639,O,0
781,anarchism,NN,IN,of,O,0.101,O,0
782,",",",",NN,anarchism,O,0,O,0
783,with,IN,",",",",O,0.98,O,0
784,those,DT,IN,with,O,0.905,O,0
785,"""",LQU,DT,those,O,0,O,0
786,who,WP,LQU,"""",O,0.974,O,0
787,often,RB,WP,who,O,0.642,O,0
788,still,RB,RB,often,O,0.861,O,0
789,have,VBP,RB,still,O,0.437,O,0
790,not,RB,VBP,have,O,0.629,O,0
791,shaken,VBN,RB,not,O,0.823,O,0
792,the,DT,VBN,shaken,O,0.895,O,0
793,sectarian,JJ,DT,the,O,0.811,O,0
794,habits,NNS,JJ,sectarian,O,0.43,O,0
795,"""",RQU,NNS,habits,O,0,O,0
796,of,IN,RQU,"""",O,0.639,O,0
797,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
798,nineteenth,JJ,DT,the,O,0.624,O,0
799,century,NN,JJ,nineteenth,O,0.204,O,0
800,contrasted,VBD,NN,century,O,0.25,O,0
801,with,IN,VBD,contrasted,O,0.98,O,0
802,the,DT,IN,with,O,0.895,O,0
803,younger,JJR,DT,the,O,0.998,O,0
804,activists,NNS,JJR,younger,O,0.067,O,0
805,who,WP,NNS,activists,O,0.974,O,0
806,are,VBP,WP,who,O,0.115,O,0
807,"""",LQU,VBP,are,O,0,O,0
808,much,RB,LQU,"""",O,0.606,O,0
809,more,RBR,RB,much,O,0.598,O,0
810,informed,JJ,RBR,more,O,0.486,O,0
811,",",",",JJ,informed,O,0,O,0
812,among,IN,",",",",O,0.097,O,0
813,other,JJ,IN,among,O,0.654,O,0
814,elements,NNS,JJ,other,O,0.335,O,0
815,",",",",NNS,elements,O,0,O,0
816,by,IN,",",",",O,0.185,O,0
817,indigenous,JJ,IN,by,O,0.478,O,0
818,",",",",JJ,indigenous,O,0,O,0
819,feminist,JJ,",",",",O,0.375,O,0
820,",",",",JJ,feminist,O,0,O,0
821,ecological,JJ,",",",",O,0.321,O,0
822,and,CC,JJ,ecological,O,0.104,O,0
823,cultural-critical,JJ,CC,and,O,0,O,0
824,ideas,NNS,JJ,cultural-critical,O,0.466,O,0
825,"""",RQU,NNS,ideas,O,0,O,0
826,",",",",RQU,"""",O,0,O,0
827,and,CC,",",",",O,0.104,O,0
828,who,WP,CC,and,O,0.974,O,0
829,by,IN,WP,who,O,0.185,O,0
830,the,DT,IN,by,O,0.895,O,0
831,turn,NN,DT,the,O,0.926,O,0
832,of,IN,NN,turn,O,0.639,O,0
833,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
834,21st,JJ,DT,the,O,0.031,O,0
835,century,NN,JJ,21st,O,0.204,O,0
836,formed,VBN,NN,century,O,0.392,O,0
837,"""",LQU,VBN,formed,O,0,O,0
838,by,IN,LQU,"""",O,0.185,O,0
839,far,RB,IN,by,O,0.369,O,0
840,the,DT,RB,far,O,0.895,O,0
841,majority,NN,DT,the,O,0.557,O,0
842,"""",RQU,NN,majority,O,0,O,0
843,of,IN,RQU,"""",O,0.639,O,0
844,anarchists,NNS,IN,of,O,0.102,O,0
845,.,.,NNS,anarchists,"O
Anarchists",0,O,0
846,became,VBD,.,.,O,0.145,"O
Anarchists",0
847,known,VBN,VBD,became,O,0.517,O,0
848,for,IN,VBN,known,O,0.389,O,0
849,their,PRP$,IN,for,O,0.896,O,0
850,involvement,NN,PRP$,their,O,0.499,O,0
851,in,IN,NN,involvement,O,0.472,O,0
852,protests,NNS,IN,in,O,0.732,O,0
853,against,IN,NNS,protests,O,0.077,O,0
854,the,DT,IN,against,O,0.895,O,0
855,meetings,NNS,DT,the,O,0.574,O,0
856,of,IN,NNS,meetings,O,0.639,O,0
857,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
858,World,NNP,DT,the,I-ORG,0.989,O,1
859,Trade,NNP,NNP,World,I-ORG,0.916,I-ORG,1
860,Organization,NNP,NNP,Trade,I-ORG,0.653,I-ORG,1
861,(,LRB,NNP,Organization,O,0,I-ORG,0
862,WTO,NNP,LRB,(,I-ORG,0.994,O,3
863,),RRB,NNP,WTO,O,0,I-ORG,0
864,",",",",RRB,),O,0,O,0
865,Group,NNP,",",",",I-ORG,0.426,O,1
866,of,IN,NNP,Group,I-ORG,0.639,I-ORG,0
867,Eight,CD,IN,of,I-ORG,0.332,I-ORG,1
868,",",",",CD,Eight,O,0,I-ORG,0
869,and,CC,",",",",O,0.104,O,0
870,the,DT,CC,and,O,0.895,O,0
871,World,NNP,DT,the,I-ORG,0.989,O,1
872,Economic,NNP,NNP,World,I-ORG,0.322,I-ORG,1
873,Forum,NNP,NNP,Economic,I-ORG,0.394,I-ORG,1
874,.,.,NNP,Forum,"O
A",0,I-ORG,0
875,landmark,JJ,.,.,O,0.523,"O
A",0
876,struggle,NN,JJ,landmark,O,0.869,O,0
877,of,IN,NN,struggle,O,0.639,O,0
878,this,DT,IN,of,O,0.903,O,0
879,period,NN,DT,this,O,0.679,O,0
880,was,VBD,NN,period,O,0.96,O,0
881,the,DT,VBD,was,O,0.895,O,0
882,confrontations,NNS,DT,the,O,0.242,O,0
883,at,IN,NNS,confrontations,O,0.125,O,0
884,WTO,NNP,IN,at,I-ORG,0.994,O,3
885,conference,NN,NNP,WTO,I-ORG,0.241,I-ORG,0
886,in,IN,NN,conference,I-ORG,0.472,I-ORG,0
887,Seattle,NNP,IN,in,I-ORG,0.809,I-ORG,1
888,in,IN,NNP,Seattle,I-ORG,0.472,I-ORG,0
889,1999,CD,IN,in,I-ORG,0.025,I-ORG,0
890,.,.,CD,1999,"O
One",0,I-ORG,0
891,reaction,NN,.,.,O,0.745,"O
One",0
892,against,IN,NN,reaction,O,0.077,O,0
893,sectarianism,NN,IN,against,O,0.812,O,0
894,within,IN,NN,sectarianism,O,0.981,O,0
895,the,DT,IN,within,O,0.895,O,0
896,anarchist,NN,DT,the,O,0.101,O,0
897,milieu,NN,NN,anarchist,O,0.584,O,0
898,was,VBD,NN,milieu,O,0.96,O,0
899,"""",LQU,VBD,was,O,0,O,0
900,anarchism,NN,LQU,"""",O,0.101,O,0
901,without,IN,NN,anarchism,O,0.982,O,0
902,adjectives,NNS,IN,without,O,0.07,O,0
903,"""",RQU,NNS,adjectives,O,0,O,0
904,",",",",RQU,"""",O,0,O,0
905,a,DT,",",",",O,0,O,0
906,call,NN,DT,a,O,0.187,O,0
907,for,IN,NN,call,O,0.389,O,0
908,toleration,NN,IN,for,O,0.911,O,0
909,first,RB,NN,toleration,O,0.383,O,0
910,adopted,VBN,RB,first,O,0.071,O,0
911,by,IN,VBN,adopted,O,0.185,O,0
912,Fernando,NNP,IN,by,I-PER,0.376,O,1
913,Tarrida,NNP,NNP,Fernando,I-PER,0.885,I-PER,1
914,del,NNP,NNP,Tarrida,I-PER,0.29,I-PER,0
915,Mármol,NNP,NNP,del,I-PER,0.609,I-PER,1
916,in,IN,NNP,Mármol,O,0.472,I-PER,0
917,1889,CD,IN,in,O,0.011,O,0
918,in,IN,CD,1889,O,0.472,O,0
919,response,NN,IN,in,O,0.777,O,0
920,to,TO,NN,response,O,0.911,O,0
921,the,DT,TO,to,O,0.895,O,0
922,"""",LQU,DT,the,O,0,O,0
923,bitter,JJ,LQU,"""",O,0.162,O,0
924,debates,NNS,JJ,bitter,O,0.283,O,0
925,"""",RQU,NNS,debates,O,0,O,0
926,of,IN,RQU,"""",O,0.639,O,0
927,anarchist,NN,IN,of,O,0.101,O,0
928,theory,NN,NN,anarchist,O,0.899,O,0
929,at,IN,NN,theory,O,0.125,O,0
930,the,DT,IN,at,O,0.895,O,0
931,time,NN,DT,the,O,0.91,O,0
932,.,.,NN,time,"O
Proudhon",0,O,0
933,proposed,VBD,.,.,O,0.728,"O
Proudhon",0
934,spontaneous,JJ,VBD,proposed,O,0.853,O,0
935,order,NN,JJ,spontaneous,O,0.652,O,0
936,",",",",NN,order,O,0,O,0
937,whereby,WRB,",",",",O,0.971,O,0
938,organization,NN,WRB,whereby,O,0.653,O,0
939,emerges,VBZ,NN,organization,O,0.338,O,0
940,without,IN,VBZ,emerges,O,0.982,O,0
941,central,JJ,IN,without,O,0.202,O,0
942,authority,NN,JJ,central,O,0.13,O,0
943,",",",",NN,authority,O,0,O,0
944,a,DT,",",",",O,0,O,0
945,"""",LQU,DT,a,O,0,O,0
946,positive,JJ,LQU,"""",O,0.703,O,0
947,anarchy,NN,JJ,positive,O,0.103,O,0
948,"""",RQU,NN,anarchy,O,0,O,0
949,where,WRB,RQU,"""",O,0.97,O,0
950,order,NN,WRB,where,O,0.652,O,0
951,arises,VBZ,NN,order,O,0.118,O,0
952,when,WRB,VBZ,arises,O,0.969,O,0
953,everybody,DT,WRB,when,O,0.353,O,0
954,does,VBZ,DT,everybody,O,0.311,O,0
955,"""",LQU,VBZ,does,O,0,O,0
956,what,WP,LQU,"""",O,0.969,O,0
957,he,PRP,WP,what,O,0.438,O,0
958,wishes,VBZ,PRP,he,O,0.979,O,0
959,and,CC,VBZ,wishes,O,0.104,O,0
960,only,RB,CC,and,O,0.645,O,0
961,what,WP,RB,only,O,0.969,O,0
962,he,PRP,WP,what,O,0.438,O,0
963,wishes,VBZ,PRP,he,O,0.979,O,0
964,"""",RQU,VBZ,wishes,O,0,O,0
965,and,CC,RQU,"""",O,0.104,O,0
966,where,WRB,CC,and,O,0.97,O,0
967,"""",LQU,WRB,where,O,0,O,0
968,business,NN,LQU,"""",O,0.184,O,0
969,transactions,NNS,NN,business,O,0.918,O,0
970,alone,RB,NNS,transactions,O,0.09,O,0
971,produce,VBP,RB,alone,O,0.718,O,0
972,the,DT,VBP,produce,O,0.895,O,0
973,social,JJ,DT,the,O,0.837,O,0
974,order,NN,JJ,social,O,0.652,O,0
975,.,.,NN,order,O,0,O,0
1036,"""",RQU,.,.,"O
Godwin",0,O,0
1037,",",",",RQU,"""",O,0,"O
Godwin",0
1038,a,DT,",",",",O,0,O,0
1039,philosophical,JJ,DT,a,O,0.685,O,0
1040,anarchist,NN,JJ,philosophical,O,0.101,O,0
1041,",",",",NN,anarchist,O,0,O,0
1042,from,IN,",",",",O,0.403,O,0
1043,a,DT,IN,from,O,0,O,0
1044,rationalist,NN,DT,a,O,0.745,O,0
1045,and,CC,NN,rationalist,O,0.104,O,0
1046,utilitarian,JJ,CC,and,O,0.939,O,0
1047,basis,NN,JJ,utilitarian,O,0.14,O,0
1048,opposed,VBD,NN,basis,O,0.649,O,0
1049,revolutionary,JJ,VBD,opposed,O,0.785,O,0
1050,action,NN,JJ,revolutionary,O,0.065,O,0
1051,and,CC,NN,action,O,0.104,O,0
1052,saw,VBD,CC,and,O,0.803,O,0
1053,a,DT,VBD,saw,O,0,O,0
1054,minimal,JJ,DT,a,O,0.589,O,0
1055,state,NN,JJ,minimal,O,0.857,O,0
1056,as,IN,NN,state,O,0.12,O,0
1057,a,DT,IN,as,O,0,O,0
1058,present,JJ,DT,a,O,0.712,O,0
1059,"""",LQU,JJ,present,O,0,O,0
1060,necessary,JJ,LQU,"""",O,0.617,O,0
1061,evil,NN,JJ,necessary,O,0.354,O,0
1062,"""",RQU,NN,evil,O,0,O,0
1063,that,WDT,RQU,"""",O,0.894,O,0
1064,would,MD,WDT,that,O,0.99,O,0
1065,become,VB,MD,would,O,0.147,O,0
1066,increasingly,RB,VB,become,O,0.476,O,0
1067,irrelevant,JJ,RB,increasingly,O,0.502,O,0
1068,and,CC,JJ,irrelevant,O,0.104,O,0
1069,powerless,JJ,CC,and,O,0.707,O,0
1070,by,IN,JJ,powerless,O,0.185,O,0
1071,the,DT,IN,by,O,0.895,O,0
1072,gradual,JJ,DT,the,O,0.42,O,0
1073,spread,NN,JJ,gradual,O,0.854,O,0
1074,of,IN,NN,spread,O,0.639,O,0
1075,knowledge,NN,IN,of,O,0.516,O,0
1076,.,.,NN,knowledge,"O
Godwin",0,O,0
1077,advocated,VBD,.,.,O,0.072,"O
Godwin",0
1078,extreme,JJ,VBD,advocated,O,0.365,O,0
1079,individualism,NN,JJ,extreme,O,0.479,O,0
1080,",",",",NN,individualism,O,0,O,0
1081,proposing,VBG,",",",",O,0.729,O,0
1082,that,IN,VBG,proposing,O,0.894,O,0
1083,all,DT,IN,that,O,0.087,O,0
1084,cooperation,NN,DT,all,O,0.255,O,0
1085,in,IN,NN,cooperation,O,0.472,O,0
1086,labour,NN,IN,in,O,0.521,O,0
1087,be,VB,NN,labour,O,0.143,O,0
1088,eliminated,VBN,VB,be,O,0.336,O,0
1089,on,IN,VBN,eliminated,O,0.644,O,0
1090,the,DT,IN,on,O,0.895,O,0
1091,premise,NN,DT,the,O,0.71,O,0
1092,that,IN,NN,premise,O,0.894,O,0
1093,this,DT,IN,that,O,0.903,O,0
1094,would,MD,DT,this,O,0.99,O,0
1095,be,VB,MD,would,O,0.143,O,0
1096,most,RBS,VB,be,O,0.599,O,0
1097,conducive,JJ,RBS,most,O,0.239,O,0
1098,with,IN,JJ,conducive,O,0.98,O,0
1099,the,DT,IN,with,O,0.895,O,0
1100,general,JJ,DT,the,O,0.409,O,0
1101,good,NN,JJ,general,O,0.418,O,0
1102,.,.,NN,good,"O
Godwin",0,O,0
1140,opposed,VBD,.,.,O,0.649,"O
Godwin",0
1141,government,NN,VBD,opposed,O,0.419,O,0
1142,because,IN,NN,government,O,0.146,O,0
1143,he,PRP,IN,because,O,0.438,O,0
1144,saw,VBD,PRP,he,O,0.803,O,0
1145,it,PRP,VBD,saw,O,0.503,O,0
1146,as,IN,PRP,it,O,0.12,O,0
1147,infringing,VBG,IN,as,O,0.487,O,0
1148,on,IN,VBG,infringing,O,0.644,O,0
1149,the,DT,IN,on,O,0.895,O,0
1150,individual,NN,DT,the,O,0.478,O,0
1151,'s,POS,NN,individual,O,0,O,0
1152,right,NN,POS,'s,O,0.787,O,0
1153,to,TO,NN,right,O,0.911,O,0
1154,"""",LQU,TO,to,O,0,O,0
1155,private,JJ,LQU,"""",O,0.717,O,0
1156,judgement,NN,JJ,private,O,0.511,O,0
1157,"""",RQU,NN,judgement,O,0,O,0
1158,to,TO,RQU,"""",O,0.911,O,0
1159,determine,VB,TO,to,O,0.298,O,0
1160,which,WDT,VB,determine,O,0.972,O,0
1161,actions,NNS,WDT,which,O,0.065,O,0
1162,most,RBS,NNS,actions,O,0.599,O,0
1163,maximise,JJ,RBS,most,O,0.568,O,0
1164,utility,NN,JJ,maximise,O,0.94,O,0
1165,",",",",NN,utility,O,0,O,0
1166,but,CC,",",",",O,0.185,O,0
1167,also,RB,CC,but,O,0.092,O,0
1168,makes,VBZ,RB,also,O,0.559,O,0
1169,a,DT,VBZ,makes,O,0,O,0
1170,critique,NN,DT,a,O,0.27,O,0
1171,of,IN,NN,critique,O,0.639,O,0
1172,all,DT,IN,of,O,0.087,O,0
1173,authority,NN,DT,all,O,0.13,O,0
1174,over,IN,NN,authority,O,0.659,O,0
1175,the,DT,IN,over,O,0.895,O,0
1176,individual,NN,DT,the,O,0.478,O,0
1177,'s,POS,NN,individual,O,0,O,0
1178,judgement,NN,POS,'s,O,0.511,O,0
1179,.,.,NN,judgement,"O
This",0,O,0
1180,aspect,NN,.,.,O,0.121,"O
This",0
1181,of,IN,NN,aspect,O,0.639,O,0
1182,Godwin,NNP,IN,of,I-PER,0.416,O,1
1183,'s,POS,NNP,Godwin,O,0,I-PER,0
1184,philosophy,NN,POS,'s,O,0.685,O,0
1185,",",",",NN,philosophy,O,0,O,0
1186,stripped,VBN,",",",",O,0.866,O,0
1187,of,IN,VBN,stripped,O,0.639,O,0
1188,utilitarian,JJ,IN,of,O,0.939,O,0
1189,motivations,NNS,JJ,utilitarian,O,0.601,O,0
1190,",",",",NNS,motivations,O,0,O,0
1191,was,VBD,",",",",O,0.96,O,0
1192,developed,VBN,VBD,was,O,0.299,O,0
1193,into,IN,VBN,developed,O,0.497,O,0
1194,a,DT,IN,into,O,0,O,0
1195,more,RBR,DT,a,O,0.598,O,0
1196,extreme,JJ,RBR,more,O,0.365,O,0
1197,form,NN,JJ,extreme,O,0.391,O,0
1198,later,RB,NN,form,O,0.528,O,0
1199,by,IN,RB,later,O,0.185,O,0
1200,Stirner,NNP,IN,by,I-PER,0.862,O,1
1201,.,.,NNP,Stirner,"O
Stirner",0,I-PER,0
1234,'s,POS,.,.,O,0,"O
Stirner",0
1235,The,DT,POS,'s,I-MISC,0.895,O,1
1236,Ego,NNP,DT,The,I-MISC,0.33,I-MISC,1
1237,and,CC,NNP,Ego,I-MISC,0.104,I-MISC,0
1238,Its,PRP$,CC,and,I-MISC,0.504,I-MISC,1
1239,Own,NNP,PRP$,Its,I-MISC,0.663,I-MISC,1
1240,",",",",NNP,Own,O,0,I-MISC,0
1241,published,VBN,",",",",O,0.736,O,0
1242,in,IN,VBN,published,O,0.472,O,0
1243,1844,CD,IN,in,O,0.01,O,0
1244,",",",",CD,1844,O,0,O,0
1245,is,VBZ,",",",",O,0.502,O,0
1246,a,DT,VBZ,is,O,0,O,0
1247,founding,JJ,DT,a,O,0.397,O,0
1248,text,NN,JJ,founding,O,0.893,O,0
1249,of,IN,NN,text,O,0.639,O,0
1250,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
1251,philosophy,NN,DT,the,O,0.685,O,0
1252,.,.,NN,philosophy,"O
To",0,O,0
1253,Stirner,VB,.,.,I-PER,0.862,"O
To",1
1254,",",",",VB,Stirner,O,0,I-PER,0
1255,rights,NNS,",",",",O,0.788,O,0
1256,were,VBD,NNS,rights,O,0.967,O,0
1257,spooks,NNS,VBD,were,O,0.853,O,0
1258,in,IN,NNS,spooks,O,0.472,O,0
1259,the,DT,IN,in,O,0.895,O,0
1260,mind,NN,DT,the,O,0.587,O,0
1261,",",",",NN,mind,O,0,O,0
1262,and,CC,",",",",O,0.104,O,0
1263,he,PRP,CC,and,O,0.438,O,0
1264,held,VBD,PRP,he,O,0.445,O,0
1265,that,IN,VBD,held,O,0.894,O,0
1266,society,NN,IN,that,O,0.84,O,0
1267,does,VBZ,NN,society,O,0.311,O,0
1268,not,RB,VBZ,does,O,0.629,O,0
1269,exist,VB,RB,not,O,0.359,O,0
1270,but,CC,VB,exist,O,0.185,O,0
1271,"""",LQU,CC,but,O,0,O,0
1272,the,DT,LQU,"""",O,0.895,O,0
1273,individuals,NNS,DT,the,O,0.481,O,0
1274,are,VBP,NNS,individuals,O,0.115,O,0
1275,its,PRP$,VBP,are,O,0.504,O,0
1276,reality,NN,PRP$,its,O,0.747,O,0
1277,"""",RQU,NN,reality,O,0,O,0
1278,.,.,RQU,"""","O
Stirner",0,O,0
1279,'s,POS,.,.,O,0,"O
Stirner",0
1280,philosophy,NN,POS,'s,O,0.685,O,0
1281,has,VBZ,NN,philosophy,O,0.436,O,0
1282,been,VBN,VBZ,has,O,0.148,O,0
1283,seen,VBN,VBN,been,O,0.813,O,0
1284,as,IN,VBN,seen,O,0.12,O,0
1285,a,DT,IN,as,O,0,O,0
1286,precedent,NN,DT,a,O,0.709,O,0
1287,of,IN,NN,precedent,O,0.639,O,0
1288,existentialism,NN,IN,of,O,0.359,O,0
1289,with,IN,NN,existentialism,O,0.98,O,0
1290,other,JJ,IN,with,O,0.654,O,0
1291,thinkers,NNS,JJ,other,O,0.902,O,0
1292,like,IN,NNS,thinkers,O,0.541,O,0
1293,Friedrich,NNP,IN,like,I-PER,0.402,O,1
1294,Nietzsche,NNP,NNP,Friedrich,I-PER,0.622,I-PER,1
1295,and,CC,NNP,Nietzsche,O,0.104,I-PER,0
1296,Søren,NNP,CC,and,I-PER,0.882,O,1
1297,Kierkegaard,NNP,NNP,Søren,I-PER,0.514,I-PER,1
1298,.,.,NNP,Kierkegaard,"O
Collectivist",0,I-PER,0
1299,anarchism,NN,.,.,O,0.101,"O
Collectivist",0
1300,",",",",NN,anarchism,O,0,O,0
1301,also,RB,",",",",O,0.092,O,0
1302,referred,VBD,RB,also,O,0.755,O,0
1303,to,TO,VBD,referred,O,0.911,O,0
1304,as,IN,TO,to,O,0.12,O,0
1305,"""",LQU,IN,as,O,0,O,0
1306,revolutionary,JJ,LQU,"""",O,0.785,O,0
1307,socialism,NN,JJ,revolutionary,O,0.838,O,0
1308,"""",RQU,NN,socialism,O,0,O,0
1309,or,CC,RQU,"""",O,0.651,O,0
1310,a,DT,CC,or,O,0,O,0
1311,form,NN,DT,a,O,0.391,O,0
1312,of,IN,NN,form,O,0.639,O,0
1313,such,JJ,IN,of,O,0.872,O,0
1314,",",",",JJ,such,O,0,O,0
1315,is,VBZ,",",",",O,0.502,O,0
1316,a,DT,VBZ,is,O,0,O,0
1317,revolutionary,JJ,DT,a,O,0.785,O,0
1318,form,NN,JJ,revolutionary,O,0.391,O,0
1319,of,IN,NN,form,O,0.639,O,0
1320,anarchism,NN,IN,of,O,0.101,O,0
1321,",",",",NN,anarchism,O,0,O,0
1322,commonly,RB,",",",",O,0.231,O,0
1323,associated,VBN,RB,commonly,O,0.123,O,0
1324,with,IN,VBN,associated,O,0.98,O,0
1325,Mikhail,NNP,IN,with,I-PER,0.582,O,1
1326,Bakunin,NNP,NNP,Mikhail,I-PER,0.134,I-PER,1
1327,and,CC,NNP,Bakunin,O,0.104,I-PER,0
1328,Johann,NNP,CC,and,I-PER,0.508,O,1
1329,Most,NNP,NNP,Johann,I-PER,0.599,I-PER,1
1330,.,.,NNP,Most,"O
It",0,I-PER,0
1331,was,VBD,.,.,O,0.96,"O
It",0
1332,inspired,VBN,VBD,was,O,0.489,O,0
1333,by,IN,VBN,inspired,O,0.185,O,0
1334,the,DT,IN,by,O,0.895,O,0
1335,late,JJ,DT,the,O,0.527,O,0
1336,19th,JJ,JJ,late,O,0.025,O,0
1337,century,NN,JJ,19th,O,0.204,O,0
1338,writings,NNS,NN,century,O,0.993,O,0
1339,of,IN,NNS,writings,O,0.639,O,0
1340,early,JJ,IN,of,O,0.32,O,0
1341,feminist,JJ,JJ,early,O,0.375,O,0
1342,anarchists,NNS,JJ,feminist,O,0.102,O,0
1343,such,JJ,NNS,anarchists,O,0.872,O,0
1344,as,IN,JJ,such,O,0.12,O,0
1345,Lucy,NNP,IN,as,I-PER,0.552,O,1
1346,Parsons,NNPS,NNP,Lucy,I-PER,0.668,I-PER,1
1347,",",",",NNPS,Parsons,O,0,I-PER,0
1348,Emma,NNP,",",",",I-PER,0.339,O,1
1349,Goldman,NNP,NNP,Emma,I-PER,0.417,I-PER,1
1350,",",",",NNP,Goldman,O,0,I-PER,0
1351,Voltairine,NNP,",",",",I-PER,0.95,O,1
1352,de,NNP,NNP,Voltairine,I-PER,0.28,I-PER,0
1353,Cleyre,NNP,NNP,de,I-PER,0.221,I-PER,1
1354,",",",",NNP,Cleyre,O,0,I-PER,0
1355,and,CC,",",",",O,0.104,O,0
1356,Dora,NNP,CC,and,I-PER,0.313,O,1
1357,Marsden,NNP,NNP,Dora,I-PER,0.563,I-PER,1
1358,.,.,NNP,Marsden,"O
It",0,I-PER,0
1359,developed,VBD,.,.,O,0.299,"O
It",0
1360,"""",LQU,VBD,developed,O,0,O,0
1361,mostly,RB,LQU,"""",O,0.6,O,0
1362,in,IN,RB,mostly,O,0.472,O,0
1363,Holland,NNP,IN,in,I-LOC,0.457,O,1
1364,",",",",NNP,Holland,O,0,I-LOC,0
1365,Britain,NNP,",",",",I-LOC,0.177,O,1
1366,",",",",NNP,Britain,O,0,I-LOC,0
1367,and,CC,",",",",O,0.104,O,0
1368,the,DT,CC,and,O,0.895,O,0
1369,U.S.,NNP,DT,the,I-LOC,0,O,2
1370,",",",",NNP,U.S.,O,0,I-LOC,0
1371,before,IN,",",",",O,0.148,O,0
1372,and,CC,IN,before,O,0.104,O,0
1373,during,IN,CC,and,O,0.317,O,0
1374,the,DT,IN,during,O,0.895,O,0
1375,Second,JJ,DT,the,I-MISC,0.81,O,1
1376,World,NNP,JJ,Second,I-MISC,0.989,I-MISC,1
1377,War,NNP,NNP,World,I-MISC,0.957,I-MISC,1
1378,"""",RQU,NNP,War,O,0,I-MISC,0
1379,.,.,RQU,"""","O
Another",0,O,0
1380,recent,JJ,.,.,O,0.752,"O
Another",0
1381,form,NN,JJ,recent,O,0.391,O,0
1382,of,IN,NN,form,O,0.639,O,0
1383,anarchism,NN,IN,of,O,0.101,O,0
1384,critical,JJ,NN,anarchism,O,0.269,O,0
1385,of,IN,JJ,critical,O,0.639,O,0
1386,formal,JJ,IN,of,O,0.391,O,0
1387,anarchist,NN,JJ,formal,O,0.101,O,0
1388,movements,NNS,NN,anarchist,O,0.606,O,0
1389,is,VBZ,NNS,movements,O,0.502,O,0
1390,insurrectionary,JJ,VBZ,is,O,0.492,O,0
1391,anarchism,NN,JJ,insurrectionary,O,0.101,O,0
1392,",",",",NN,anarchism,O,0,O,0
1393,which,WDT,",",",",O,0.972,O,0
1394,advocates,VBZ,WDT,which,O,0.073,O,0
1395,informal,JJ,VBZ,advocates,O,0.486,O,0
1396,organization,NN,JJ,informal,O,0.653,O,0
1397,and,CC,NN,organization,O,0.104,O,0
1398,active,JJ,CC,and,O,0.066,O,0
1399,resistance,NN,JJ,active,O,0.773,O,0
1400,to,TO,NN,resistance,O,0.911,O,0
1401,the,DT,TO,to,O,0.895,O,0
1402,state,NN,DT,the,O,0.857,O,0
1403,;,;,NN,state,O,0,O,0
1404,its,PRP$,;,;,O,0.504,O,0
1405,proponents,NNS,PRP$,its,O,0.727,O,0
1406,include,VBP,NNS,proponents,O,0.473,O,0
1407,Wolfi,NNP,VBP,include,I-PER,0.983,O,1
1408,Landstreicher,NNP,NNP,Wolfi,I-PER,0.524,I-PER,1
1409,and,CC,NNP,Landstreicher,O,0.104,I-PER,0
1410,Alfredo,NNP,CC,and,I-PER,0.087,O,1
1411,M.,NNP,NNP,Alfredo,I-PER,0,I-PER,1
1412,Bonanno,NNP,NNP,M.,I-PER,0.169,I-PER,1
1413,.,.,NNP,Bonanno,"O
Free",0,I-PER,0
1414,love,NN,.,.,O,0.549,"O
Free",0
1415,advocates,NNS,NN,love,O,0.073,O,0
1416,sometimes,RB,NNS,advocates,O,0.842,O,0
1417,traced,VBD,RB,sometimes,O,0.916,O,0
1418,their,PRP$,VBD,traced,O,0.896,O,0
1419,roots,NNS,PRP$,their,O,0.795,O,0
1420,back,RB,NNS,roots,O,0.133,O,0
1421,to,TO,RB,back,O,0.911,O,0
1422,Josiah,NNP,TO,to,I-PER,0.51,O,1
1423,Warren,NNP,NNP,Josiah,I-PER,0.959,I-PER,1
1424,and,CC,NNP,Warren,O,0.104,I-PER,0
1425,to,TO,CC,and,O,0.911,O,0
1426,experimental,JJ,TO,to,O,0.361,O,0
1427,communities,NNS,JJ,experimental,O,0.232,O,0
1428,",",",",NNS,communities,O,0,O,0
1429,viewed,VBD,",",",",O,0.947,O,0
1430,sexual,JJ,VBD,viewed,O,0.821,O,0
1431,freedom,NN,JJ,sexual,O,0.4,O,0
1432,as,IN,NN,freedom,O,0.12,O,0
1433,a,DT,IN,as,O,0,O,0
1434,clear,JJ,DT,a,O,0.221,O,0
1435,",",",",JJ,clear,O,0,O,0
1436,direct,JJ,",",",",O,0.303,O,0
1437,expression,NN,JJ,direct,O,0.364,O,0
1438,of,IN,NN,expression,O,0.639,O,0
1439,an,DT,IN,of,O,0.1,O,0
1440,individual,NN,DT,an,O,0.478,O,0
1441,'s,POS,NN,individual,O,0,O,0
1442,self-ownership,NN,POS,'s,O,0,O,0
1443,.,.,NN,self-ownership,"O
In",0,O,0
1444,New,NNP,.,.,I-LOC,0.621,"O
In",1
1445,York,NNP,NNP,New,I-LOC,0.997,I-LOC,1
1446,'s,POS,NNP,York,O,0,I-LOC,0
1447,Greenwich,NNP,POS,'s,I-LOC,0.424,O,1
1448,Village,NNP,NNP,Greenwich,I-LOC,0.948,I-LOC,1
1449,",",",",NNP,Village,O,0,I-LOC,0
1450,bohemian,JJ,",",",",O,0.167,O,0
1451,feminists,NNS,JJ,bohemian,O,0.375,O,0
1452,and,CC,NNS,feminists,O,0.104,O,0
1453,socialists,NNS,CC,and,O,0.839,O,0
1454,advocated,VBN,NNS,socialists,O,0.072,O,0
1455,self-realisation,NN,VBN,advocated,O,0,O,0
1456,and,CC,NN,self-realisation,O,0.104,O,0
1457,pleasure,NN,CC,and,O,0.693,O,0
1458,for,IN,NN,pleasure,O,0.389,O,0
1459,women,NNS,IN,for,O,0.984,O,0
1460,(,LRB,NNS,women,O,0,O,0
1461,and,CC,LRB,(,O,0.104,O,0
1462,also,RB,CC,and,O,0.092,O,0
1463,men,NNS,RB,also,O,0.577,O,0
1464,),RRB,NNS,men,O,0,O,0
1465,in,IN,RRB,),O,0.472,O,0
1466,the,DT,IN,in,O,0.895,O,0
1467,here,RB,DT,the,O,0.448,O,0
1468,and,CC,RB,here,O,0.104,O,0
1469,now,RB,CC,and,O,0.634,O,0
1470,.,.,RB,now,"O
They",0,O,0
1471,encouraged,VBD,.,.,O,0.341,"O
They",0
1472,playing,VBG,VBD,encouraged,O,0.692,O,0
1473,with,IN,VBG,playing,O,0.98,O,0
1474,sexual,JJ,IN,with,O,0.821,O,0
1475,roles,NNS,JJ,sexual,O,0.794,O,0
1476,and,CC,NNS,roles,O,0.104,O,0
1477,sexuality,NN,CC,and,O,0.822,O,0
1478,",",",",NN,sexuality,O,0,O,0
1479,and,CC,",",",",O,0.104,O,0
1480,the,DT,CC,and,O,0.895,O,0
1481,openly,RB,DT,the,O,0.647,O,0
1482,bisexual,JJ,RB,openly,O,0.161,O,0
1483,radical,JJ,JJ,bisexual,O,0.739,O,0
1484,Edna,NNP,JJ,radical,I-PER,0.325,O,1
1485,St.,NNP,NNP,Edna,I-PER,0,I-PER,1
1486,Vincent,NNP,NNP,St.,I-PER,0.948,I-PER,1
1487,Millay,NNP,NNP,Vincent,I-PER,0.586,I-PER,1
1488,and,CC,NNP,Millay,O,0.104,I-PER,0
1489,the,DT,CC,and,O,0.895,O,0
1490,lesbian,JJ,DT,the,O,0.536,O,0
1491,anarchist,NN,JJ,lesbian,O,0.101,O,0
1492,Margaret,NNP,NN,anarchist,I-PER,0.562,O,1
1493,Anderson,NNP,NNP,Margaret,I-PER,0.104,I-PER,1
1494,were,VBD,NNP,Anderson,O,0.967,I-PER,0
1495,prominent,JJ,VBD,were,O,0.723,O,0
1496,among,IN,JJ,prominent,O,0.097,O,0
1497,them,PRP,IN,among,O,0.896,O,0
1498,.,.,PRP,them,"O
1531,"""",RQU,.,.,"O
Max",0,O,0
1532,Stirner,NNP,RQU,"""",I-PER,0.862,"O
Max",1
1533,wrote,VBD,NNP,Stirner,O,0.993,I-PER,0
1534,in,IN,VBD,wrote,O,0.472,O,0
1535,1842,CD,IN,in,O,0.009,O,0
1536,a,DT,CD,1842,O,0,O,0
1537,long,JJ,DT,a,O,0.546,O,0
1538,essay,NN,JJ,long,O,0.35,O,0
1539,on,IN,NN,essay,O,0.644,O,0
1540,education,NN,IN,on,O,0.326,O,0
1541,called,VBN,NN,education,O,0.188,O,0
1542,The,DT,VBN,called,I-MISC,0.895,O,1
1543,False,NNP,DT,The,I-MISC,0.367,I-MISC,1
1544,Principle,NN,NNP,False,I-MISC,0.716,I-MISC,1
1545,of,IN,NN,Principle,I-MISC,0.639,I-MISC,0
1546,our,PRP$,IN,of,I-MISC,0.656,I-MISC,0
1547,Education,NN,PRP$,our,I-MISC,0.326,I-MISC,1
1548,.,.,NN,Education,"O
In",0,I-MISC,0
1549,it,PRP,.,.,O,0.503,"O
In",0
1550,Stirner,JJR,PRP,it,I-PER,0.862,O,1
1551,names,NNS,JJR,Stirner,O,0.612,I-PER,0
1552,his,PRP$,NNS,names,O,0.453,O,0
1553,educational,JJ,PRP$,his,O,0.326,O,0
1554,principle,NN,JJ,educational,O,0.716,O,0
1555,"""",LQU,NN,principle,O,0,O,0
1556,"personalist,",VBZ,LQU,"""",O,0,O,0
1557,"""",RQU,VBZ,"personalist,",O,0,O,0
1558,explaining,VBG,RQU,"""",O,0.362,O,0
1559,that,DT,VBG,explaining,O,0.894,O,0
1560,self-understanding,NN,DT,that,O,0,O,0
1561,consists,VBZ,NN,self-understanding,O,0.247,O,0
1562,in,IN,VBZ,consists,O,0.472,O,0
1563,hourly,JJ,IN,in,O,0.461,O,0
1564,self-creation,NN,JJ,hourly,O,0,O,0
1565,.,.,NN,self-creation,"O
1601,"""",RQU,.,.,"O
The",0,O,0
1602,first,NN,RQU,"""",O,0.383,"O
The",0
1603,of,IN,NN,first,O,0.639,O,0
1604,these,DT,IN,of,O,0.9,O,0
1605,was,VBD,DT,these,O,0.96,O,0
1606,started,VBN,VBD,was,O,0.856,O,0
1607,in,IN,VBN,started,O,0.472,O,0
1608,New,NNP,IN,in,I-LOC,0.621,O,1
1609,York,NNP,NNP,New,I-LOC,0.997,I-LOC,1
1610,City,NNP,NNP,York,I-LOC,0.217,I-LOC,1
1611,in,IN,NNP,City,O,0.472,I-LOC,0
1612,1911,CD,IN,in,O,0.014,O,0
1613,.,.,CD,1911,"O
Summerhill",0,O,0
1614,is,VBZ,.,.,O,0.502,"O
Summerhill",0
1615,often,RB,VBZ,is,O,0.642,O,0
1616,cited,VBN,RB,often,O,0.217,O,0
1617,as,IN,VBN,cited,O,0.12,O,0
1618,an,DT,IN,as,O,0.1,O,0
1619,example,NN,DT,an,O,0.355,O,0
1620,of,IN,NN,example,O,0.639,O,0
1621,anarchism,NN,IN,of,O,0.101,O,0
1622,in,IN,NN,anarchism,O,0.472,O,0
1623,practice,NN,IN,in,O,0.708,O,0
1624,.,.,NN,practice,"O
The",0,O,0
1625,term,NN,.,.,O,0.892,"O
The",0
1626,deschooling,NN,NN,term,O,0.297,O,0
1627,was,VBD,NN,deschooling,O,0.96,O,0
1628,popularized,VBN,VBD,was,O,0.7,O,0
1629,by,IN,VBN,popularized,O,0.185,O,0
1630,Ivan,NNP,IN,by,I-PER,0.506,O,1
1631,Illich,NNP,NNP,Ivan,I-PER,0.468,I-PER,1
1632,",",",",NNP,Illich,O,0,I-PER,0
1633,who,WP,",",",",O,0.974,O,0
1634,argued,VBD,WP,who,O,0.117,O,0
1635,that,IN,VBD,argued,O,0.894,O,0
1636,the,DT,IN,that,O,0.895,O,0
1637,school,NN,DT,the,O,0.806,O,0
1638,as,IN,NN,school,O,0.12,O,0
1639,an,DT,IN,as,O,0.1,O,0
1640,institution,NN,DT,an,O,0.491,O,0
1641,is,VBZ,NN,institution,O,0.502,O,0
1642,dysfunctional,JJ,VBZ,is,O,0.318,O,0
1643,for,IN,JJ,dysfunctional,O,0.389,O,0
1644,self-determined,JJ,IN,for,O,0,O,0
1645,learning,NN,JJ,self-determined,O,0.53,O,0
1646,and,CC,NN,learning,O,0.104,O,0
1647,serves,VBZ,CC,and,O,0.817,O,0
1648,the,DT,VBZ,serves,O,0.895,O,0
1649,creation,NN,DT,the,O,0.268,O,0
1650,of,IN,NN,creation,O,0.639,O,0
1651,a,DT,IN,of,O,0,O,0
1652,consumer,NN,DT,a,O,0.249,O,0
1653,society,NN,NN,consumer,O,0.84,O,0
1654,instead,RB,NN,society,O,0.49,O,0
1655,.,.,RB,instead,"O

According",0,O,0
1656,to,TO,.,.,O,0.911,"O

According",0
1657,Luther,NNP,TO,to,I-PER,0.554,O,1
1658,'s,POS,NNP,Luther,O,0,I-PER,0
1659,notetaker,NN,POS,'s,O,0.631,O,0
1660,Mathesius,NNP,NN,notetaker,I-PER,0.567,O,1
1661,",",",",NNP,Mathesius,O,0,I-PER,0
1662,Luther,NNP,",",",",I-PER,0.554,O,1
1663,thought,VBD,NNP,Luther,O,0.906,I-PER,0
1664,the,DT,VBD,thought,O,0.895,O,0
1665,boy,NN,DT,the,O,0.172,O,0
1666,was,VBD,NN,boy,O,0.96,O,0
1667,a,DT,VBD,was,O,0,O,0
1668,soulless,JJ,DT,a,O,0.844,O,0
1669,mass,NN,JJ,soulless,O,0.566,O,0
1670,of,IN,NN,mass,O,0.639,O,0
1671,flesh,NN,IN,of,O,0.384,O,0
1672,possessed,VBN,NN,flesh,O,0.703,O,0
1673,by,IN,VBN,possessed,O,0.185,O,0
1674,the,DT,IN,by,O,0.895,O,0
1675,devil,NN,DT,the,O,0.3,O,0
1676,",",",",NN,devil,O,0,O,0
1677,and,CC,",",",",O,0.104,O,0
1678,suggested,VBD,CC,and,O,0.875,O,0
1679,that,IN,VBD,suggested,O,0.894,O,0
1680,he,PRP,IN,that,O,0.438,O,0
1681,be,VB,PRP,he,O,0.143,O,0
1682,suffocated,VBN,VB,be,O,0.873,O,0
1683,.,.,VBN,suffocated,"O
Kanner",0,O,0
1721,'s,POS,.,.,O,0,"O
Kanner",0
1722,reuse,NN,POS,'s,O,0.782,O,0
1723,of,IN,NN,reuse,O,0.639,O,0
1724,autism,NN,IN,of,O,0.13,O,0
1725,led,VBD,NN,autism,O,0.532,O,0
1726,to,TO,VBD,led,O,0.911,O,0
1727,decades,NNS,TO,to,O,0.284,O,0
1728,of,IN,NNS,decades,O,0.639,O,0
1729,confused,JJ,IN,of,O,0.243,O,0
1730,terminology,NN,JJ,confused,O,0.893,O,0
1731,like,IN,NN,terminology,O,0.541,O,0
1732,infantile,JJ,IN,like,O,0.483,O,0
1733,schizophrenia,NN,JJ,infantile,O,0.805,O,0
1734,",",",",NN,schizophrenia,O,0,O,0
1735,and,CC,",",",",O,0.104,O,0
1736,child,NN,CC,and,O,0.213,O,0
1737,psychiatry,NN,NN,child,O,0.734,O,0
1738,'s,POS,NN,psychiatry,O,0,O,0
1739,focus,NN,POS,'s,O,0.386,O,0
1740,on,IN,NN,focus,O,0.644,O,0
1741,maternal,JJ,IN,on,O,0.566,O,0
1742,deprivation,NN,JJ,maternal,O,0.295,O,0
1743,led,VBD,NN,deprivation,O,0.532,O,0
1744,to,TO,VBD,led,O,0.911,O,0
1745,misconceptions,NNS,TO,to,O,0.59,O,0
1746,of,IN,NNS,misconceptions,O,0.639,O,0
1747,autism,NN,IN,of,O,0.13,O,0
1748,as,IN,NN,autism,O,0.12,O,0
1749,an,DT,IN,as,O,0.1,O,0
1750,infant,NN,DT,an,O,0.482,O,0
1751,'s,POS,NN,infant,O,0,O,0
1752,response,NN,POS,'s,O,0.777,O,0
1753,to,TO,NN,response,O,0.911,O,0
1754,"""",LQU,TO,to,O,0,O,0
1755,refrigerator,NN,LQU,"""",O,0.758,O,0
1756,mothers,NNS,NN,refrigerator,O,0.601,O,0
1757,"""",RQU,NNS,mothers,O,0,O,0
1758,.,.,RQU,"""","O
The",0,O,0
1759,Internet,NNP,.,.,I-MISC,0.495,"O
The",1
1760,has,VBZ,NNP,Internet,O,0.436,I-MISC,0
1761,helped,VBN,VBZ,has,O,0.445,O,0
1762,autistic,JJ,VBN,helped,O,0.131,O,0
1763,individuals,NNS,JJ,autistic,O,0.481,O,0
1764,bypass,VBP,NNS,individuals,O,0.186,O,0
1765,nonverbal,JJ,VBP,bypass,O,0.626,O,0
1766,cues,NNS,JJ,nonverbal,O,0.271,O,0
1767,and,CC,NNS,cues,O,0.104,O,0
1768,emotional,JJ,CC,and,O,0.34,O,0
1769,sharing,NN,JJ,emotional,O,0.824,O,0
1770,that,IN,NN,sharing,O,0.894,O,0
1771,they,PRP,IN,that,O,0.902,O,0
1772,find,VBP,PRP,they,O,0.382,O,0
1773,so,SO,VBP,find,O,0.837,O,0
1774,hard,JJ,SO,so,O,0.435,O,0
1775,to,TO,JJ,hard,O,0.911,O,0
1776,deal,VB,TO,to,O,0.282,O,0
1777,with,IN,VB,deal,O,0.98,O,0
1778,",",",",IN,with,O,0,O,0
1779,and,CC,",",",",O,0.104,O,0
1780,has,VBZ,CC,and,O,0.436,O,0
1781,given,VBN,VBZ,has,O,0.414,O,0
1782,them,PRP,VBN,given,O,0.896,O,0
1783,a,DT,PRP,them,O,0,O,0
1784,way,NN,DT,a,O,0.961,O,0
1785,to,TO,NN,way,O,0.911,O,0
1786,form,VB,TO,to,O,0.391,O,0
1787,online,JJ,VB,form,O,0.645,O,0
1788,communities,NNS,JJ,online,O,0.232,O,0
1789,and,CC,NNS,communities,O,0.104,O,0
1790,work,NN,CC,and,O,0.987,O,0
1791,remotely,RB,NN,work,O,0.767,O,0
1792,.,.,RB,remotely,"O

Another",0,O,0
1793,notable,JJ,.,.,O,0.63,"O

Another",0
1794,high,JJ,JJ,notable,O,0.449,O,0
1795,albedo,NN,JJ,high,O,0.084,O,0
1796,body,NN,NN,albedo,O,0.166,O,0
1797,is,VBZ,NN,body,O,0.502,O,0
1798,Eris,NNP,VBZ,is,I-LOC,0.347,O,1
1799,",",",",NNP,Eris,O,0,I-LOC,0
1800,with,IN,",",",",O,0.98,O,0
1801,an,DT,IN,with,O,0.1,O,0
1802,albedo,NN,DT,an,O,0.084,O,0
1803,of,IN,NN,albedo,O,0.639,O,0
1804,0.86,CD,IN,of,O,0,O,0
1805,.,.,CD,0.86,"O
Alabama",0,O,0
1928,ranks,VBZ,.,.,O,0.742,"O
Alabama",0
1929,30th,JJ,VBZ,ranks,O,0.036,O,0
1930,in,IN,JJ,30th,O,0.472,O,0
1931,total,JJ,IN,in,O,0.914,O,0
1932,land,NN,JJ,total,O,0.522,O,0
1933,area,NN,NN,land,O,0.115,O,0
1934,and,CC,NN,area,O,0.104,O,0
1935,ranks,VBZ,CC,and,O,0.742,O,0
1936,second,JJ,VBZ,ranks,O,0.81,O,0
1937,in,IN,JJ,second,O,0.472,O,0
1938,the,DT,IN,in,O,0.895,O,0
1939,size,NN,DT,the,O,0.832,O,0
1940,of,IN,NN,size,O,0.639,O,0
1941,its,PRP$,IN,of,O,0.504,O,0
1942,inland,NN,PRP$,its,O,0.488,O,0
1943,waterways,NNS,NN,inland,O,0.96,O,0
1944,.,.,NNS,waterways,"O
Scholars",0,I-PER,0
2053,believe,VBP,.,.,O,0.152,"O
Scholars",0
2054,the,DT,VBP,believe,O,0.895,O,0
2055,word,NN,DT,the,O,0.986,O,0
2056,comes,VBZ,NN,word,O,0.229,O,0
2057,from,IN,VBZ,comes,O,0.403,O,0
2058,the,DT,IN,from,O,0.895,O,0
2059,Choctaw,NNP,DT,the,I-MISC,0.214,O,1
2060,alba,NN,NNP,Choctaw,O,0.084,I-MISC,0
2061,(,LRB,NN,alba,O,0,O,0
2062,meaning,VBG,LRB,(,O,0.571,O,0
2063,"""",LQU,VBG,meaning,O,0,O,0
2064,plants,NNS,LQU,"""",O,0.691,O,0
2065,"""",RQU,NNS,plants,O,0,O,0
2066,or,CC,RQU,"""",O,0.651,O,0
2067,"""",LQU,CC,or,O,0,O,0
2068,weeds,NNS,LQU,"""",O,0.965,O,0
2069,"""",RQU,NNS,weeds,O,0,O,0
2070,),RRB,RQU,"""",O,0,O,0
2071,and,CC,RRB,),O,0.104,O,0
2072,amo,NN,CC,and,O,0.097,O,0
2073,(,LRB,NN,amo,O,0,O,0
2074,meaning,VBG,LRB,(,O,0.571,O,0
2075,"""",LQU,VBG,meaning,O,0,O,0
2076,to,TO,LQU,"""",O,0.911,O,0
2077,cut,VB,TO,to,O,0.274,O,0
2078,"""",RQU,VB,cut,O,0,O,0
2079,",",",",RQU,"""",O,0,O,0
2080,"""",LQU,",",",",O,0,O,0
2081,to,TO,LQU,"""",O,0.911,O,0
2082,trim,VB,TO,to,O,0.922,O,0
2083,"""",RQU,VB,trim,O,0,O,0
2084,",",",",RQU,"""",O,0,O,0
2085,or,CC,",",",",O,0.651,O,0
2086,"""",LQU,CC,or,O,0,O,0
2087,to,TO,LQU,"""",O,0.911,O,0
2088,gather,VB,TO,to,O,0.408,O,0
2089,"""",RQU,VB,gather,O,0,O,0
2090,),RRB,RQU,"""",O,0,O,0
2091,.,.,RRB,),"O
The",0,O,0
2104,economy,NN,.,.,O,0.323,"O
The",0
2105,of,IN,NN,economy,O,0.639,O,0
2106,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
2107,central,JJ,DT,the,O,0.202,O,0
2108,"""",LQU,JJ,central,O,0,O,0
2109,Black,NNP,LQU,"""",I-LOC,0.162,O,1
2110,Belt,NNP,NNP,Black,I-LOC,0.154,I-LOC,1
2111,"""",RQU,NNP,Belt,O,0,I-LOC,0
2112,was,VBD,RQU,"""",O,0.96,O,0
2113,built,VBN,VBD,was,O,0.179,O,0
2114,around,IN,VBN,built,O,0.119,O,0
2115,large,JJ,IN,around,O,0.525,O,0
2116,cotton,NN,JJ,large,O,0.259,O,0
2117,plantations,NNS,NN,cotton,O,0.689,O,0
2118,whose,WP$,NNS,plantations,O,0.975,O,0
2119,owners,NNS,WP$,whose,O,0.663,O,0
2120,built,VBD,NNS,owners,O,0.179,O,0
2121,their,PRP$,VBD,built,O,0.896,O,0
2122,wealth,NN,PRP$,their,O,0.963,O,0
2123,on,IN,NN,wealth,O,0.644,O,0
2124,slave,JJ,IN,on,O,0.833,O,0
2125,labor,NN,JJ,slave,O,0.52,O,0
2126,.,.,NN,labor,"O
While",0,O,0
2127,few,JJ,.,.,O,0.378,"O
While",0
2128,battles,NNS,JJ,few,O,0.141,O,0
2129,were,VBD,NNS,battles,O,0.967,O,0
2130,fought,VBN,VBD,were,O,0.395,O,0
2131,in,IN,VBN,fought,O,0.472,O,0
2132,the,DT,IN,in,O,0.895,O,0
2133,state,NN,DT,the,O,0.857,O,0
2134,",",",",NN,state,O,0,O,0
2135,Alabama,NNP,",",",",I-LOC,0.083,O,1
2136,contributed,VBD,NNP,Alabama,O,0.251,I-LOC,0
2137,about,IN,VBD,contributed,O,0.056,O,0
2138,"120,000",CD,IN,about,O,0,O,0
2139,soldiers,NNS,CD,"120,000",O,0.84,O,0
2140,to,TO,NNS,soldiers,O,0.911,O,0
2141,the,DT,TO,to,O,0.895,O,0
2142,American,NNP,DT,the,I-MISC,0.096,O,1
2143,Civil,NNP,NNP,American,I-MISC,0.218,I-MISC,1
2144,War,NNP,NNP,Civil,I-MISC,0.957,I-MISC,1
2145,.,.,NNP,War,"O
After",0,I-MISC,0
2146,the,DT,.,.,O,0.895,"O
After",0
2147,Civil,NNP,DT,the,I-MISC,0.218,O,1
2148,War,NNP,NNP,Civil,I-MISC,0.957,I-MISC,1
2149,",",",",NNP,War,O,0,I-MISC,0
2150,the,DT,",",",",O,0.895,O,0
2151,state,NN,DT,the,O,0.857,O,0
2152,was,VBD,NN,state,O,0.96,O,0
2153,still,RB,VBD,was,O,0.861,O,0
2154,chiefly,RB,RB,still,O,0.212,O,0
2155,agricultural,JJ,RB,chiefly,O,0.078,O,0
2156,",",",",JJ,agricultural,O,0,O,0
2157,with,IN,",",",",O,0.98,O,0
2158,an,DT,IN,with,O,0.1,O,0
2159,economy,NN,DT,an,O,0.323,O,0
2160,tied,VBN,NN,economy,O,0.909,O,0
2161,to,TO,VBN,tied,O,0.911,O,0
2162,cotton,NN,TO,to,O,0.259,O,0
2163,.,.,NN,cotton,"O
In",0,O,0
2164,1900,CD,.,.,O,0.013,"O
In",0
2165,",",",",CD,1900,O,0,O,0
2166,fourteen,CD,",",",",O,0.398,O,0
2167,Black,NNP,CD,fourteen,I-LOC,0.162,O,1
2168,Belt,NNP,NNP,Black,I-LOC,0.154,I-LOC,1
2169,counties,NNS,NNP,Belt,O,0.262,I-LOC,0
2170,had,VBD,NNS,counties,O,0.431,O,0
2171,more,JJR,VBD,had,O,0.598,O,0
2172,than,IN,JJR,more,O,0.894,O,0
2173,"79,000",CD,IN,than,O,0,O,0
2174,voters,NNS,CD,"79,000",O,0.952,O,0
2175,on,IN,NNS,voters,O,0.644,O,0
2176,the,DT,IN,on,O,0.895,O,0
2177,rolls,NNS,DT,the,O,0.794,O,0
2178,.,.,NNS,rolls,"O
The",0,O,0
2179,Voting,NNP,.,.,I-MISC,0.953,"O
The",1
2180,Rights,NNP,NNP,Voting,I-MISC,0.788,I-MISC,1
2181,Act,NNP,NNP,Rights,I-MISC,0.064,I-MISC,1
2182,of,IN,NNP,Act,I-MISC,0.639,I-MISC,0
2183,1965,CD,IN,of,I-MISC,0.021,I-MISC,0
2184,also,RB,CD,1965,O,0.092,I-MISC,0
2185,protected,VBD,RB,also,O,0.73,O,0
2186,the,DT,VBD,protected,O,0.895,O,0
2187,suffrage,NN,DT,the,O,0.874,O,0
2188,of,IN,NN,suffrage,O,0.639,O,0
2189,poor,JJ,IN,of,O,0.698,O,0
2190,whites,NNS,JJ,poor,O,0.973,O,0
2191,.,.,NNS,whites,"O
The",0,O,0
2192,population,NN,.,.,O,0.7,"O
The",0
2193,growth,NN,NN,population,O,0.427,O,0
2194,rate,NN,NN,growth,O,0.744,O,0
2195,in,IN,NN,rate,O,0.472,O,0
2196,Ala.,NNP,IN,in,I-LOC,0,O,1
2197,dropped,VBD,NNP,Ala.,O,0.315,I-LOC,0
2198,by,IN,VBD,dropped,O,0.185,O,0
2199,nearly,RB,IN,by,O,0.616,O,0
2200,half,NN,RB,nearly,O,0.432,O,0
2201,from,IN,NN,half,O,0.403,O,0
2202,1910,CD,IN,from,O,0.013,O,0
2203,--,:,CD,1910,O,0,O,0
2204,1920,CD,:,--,O,0.016,O,0
2205,",",",",CD,1920,O,0,O,0
2206,reflecting,VBG,",",",",O,0.756,O,0
2207,the,DT,VBG,reflecting,O,0.895,O,0
2208,effect,NN,DT,the,O,0.327,O,0
2209,of,IN,NN,effect,O,0.639,O,0
2210,emigration,NN,IN,of,O,0.338,O,0
2211,.,.,NN,emigration,"O
At",0,O,0
2212,the,DT,.,.,O,0.895,"O
At",0
2213,same,JJ,DT,the,O,0.802,O,0
2214,time,NN,JJ,same,O,0.91,O,0
2215,",",",",NN,time,O,0,O,0
2216,many,JJ,",",",",O,0.56,O,0
2217,rural,JJ,JJ,many,O,0.798,O,0
2218,whites,NNS,JJ,rural,O,0.973,O,0
2219,and,CC,NNS,whites,O,0.104,O,0
2220,blacks,NNS,CC,and,O,0.163,O,0
2221,migrated,VBD,NNS,blacks,O,0.581,O,0
2222,to,TO,VBD,migrated,O,0.911,O,0
2223,the,DT,TO,to,O,0.895,O,0
2224,city,NN,DT,the,O,0.217,O,0
2225,of,IN,NN,city,O,0.639,O,0
2226,Birmingham,NNP,IN,of,I-LOC,0.16,O,1
2227,for,IN,NNP,Birmingham,O,0.389,I-LOC,0
2228,work,NN,IN,for,O,0.987,O,0
2229,in,IN,NN,work,O,0.472,O,0
2230,new,JJ,IN,in,O,0.621,O,0
2231,industrial,JJ,JJ,new,O,0.481,O,0
2232,jobs,NNS,JJ,industrial,O,0.508,O,0
2233,.,.,NNS,jobs,"O
It",0,O,0
2234,experienced,VBD,.,.,O,0.36,"O
It",0
2235,such,JJ,VBD,experienced,O,0.872,O,0
2236,rapid,JJ,JJ,such,O,0.743,O,0
2237,growth,NN,JJ,rapid,O,0.427,O,0
2238,that,IN,NN,growth,O,0.894,O,0
2239,it,PRP,IN,that,O,0.503,O,0
2240,was,VBD,PRP,it,O,0.96,O,0
2241,nicknamed,VBN,VBD,was,O,0.622,O,0
2242,"""",LQU,VBN,nicknamed,O,0,O,0
2243,The,DT,LQU,"""",O,0.895,O,1
2244,Magic,NNP,DT,The,I-LOC,0.555,O,1
2245,City,NNP,NNP,Magic,I-LOC,0.217,I-LOC,1
2246,"""",RQU,NNP,City,O,0,I-LOC,0
2247,.,.,RQU,"""","O
In",0,O,0
2273,addition,NN,.,.,O,0.068,"O
In",0
2274,",",",",NN,addition,O,0,O,0
2275,the,DT,",",",",O,0.895,O,0
2276,state,NN,DT,the,O,0.857,O,0
2277,legislature,NN,NN,state,O,0.534,O,0
2278,gerrymandered,VBD,NN,legislature,O,0.413,O,0
2279,the,DT,VBD,gerrymandered,O,0.895,O,0
2280,few,JJ,DT,the,O,0.378,O,0
2281,Birmingham,NNP,JJ,few,I-LOC,0.16,O,1
2282,legislative,JJ,NNP,Birmingham,O,0.534,I-LOC,0
2283,seats,NNS,JJ,legislative,O,0.809,O,0
2284,to,TO,NNS,seats,O,0.911,O,0
2285,ensure,VB,TO,to,O,0.343,O,0
2286,election,NN,VB,ensure,O,0.333,O,0
2287,by,IN,NN,election,O,0.185,O,0
2288,persons,NNS,IN,by,O,0.682,O,0
2289,living,VBG,NNS,persons,O,0.545,O,0
2290,outside,IN,VBG,living,O,0.658,O,0
2291,Birmingham,NNP,IN,outside,I-LOC,0.16,O,1
2292,.,.,NNP,Birmingham,"O
One",0,I-LOC,0
2293,result,NN,.,.,O,0.778,"O
One",0
2294,was,VBD,NN,result,O,0.96,O,0
2295,that,IN,VBD,was,O,0.894,O,0
2296,Jefferson,NNP,IN,that,I-LOC,0.507,O,1
2297,County,NNP,NNP,Jefferson,I-LOC,0.263,I-LOC,1
2298,",",",",NNP,County,O,0,I-LOC,0
2299,containing,VBG,",",",",O,0.25,O,0
2300,Birmingham,NNP,VBG,containing,I-LOC,0.16,O,1
2301,'s,POS,NNP,Birmingham,O,0,I-LOC,0
2302,industrial,JJ,POS,'s,O,0.481,O,0
2303,and,CC,JJ,industrial,O,0.104,O,0
2304,economic,JJ,CC,and,O,0.322,O,0
2305,powerhouse,NN,JJ,economic,O,0.706,O,0
2306,",",",",NN,powerhouse,O,0,O,0
2307,contributed,VBD,",",",",O,0.251,O,0
2308,more,JJR,VBD,contributed,O,0.598,O,0
2309,than,IN,JJR,more,O,0.894,O,0
2310,one-third,NN,IN,than,O,0,O,0
2311,of,IN,NN,one-third,O,0.639,O,0
2312,all,DT,IN,of,O,0.087,O,0
2313,tax,NN,DT,all,O,0.885,O,0
2314,revenue,NN,NN,tax,O,0.782,O,0
2315,to,TO,NN,revenue,O,0.911,O,0
2316,the,DT,TO,to,O,0.895,O,0
2317,state,NN,DT,the,O,0.857,O,0
2318,",",",",NN,state,O,0,O,0
2319,but,CC,",",",",O,0.185,O,0
2320,did,VBD,CC,but,O,0.302,O,0
2321,not,RB,VBD,did,O,0.629,O,0
2322,received,VBN,RB,not,O,0.75,O,0
2323,a,DT,VBN,received,O,0,O,0
2324,proportional,JJ,DT,a,O,0.727,O,0
2325,amount,NN,JJ,proportional,O,0.098,O,0
2326,in,IN,NN,amount,O,0.472,O,0
2327,services,NNS,IN,in,O,0.818,O,0
2328,.,.,NNS,services,"O
A",0,O,0
2329,1960,CD,.,.,O,0.02,"O
A",0
2330,study,NN,CD,1960,O,0.87,O,0
2331,noted,VBD,NN,study,O,0.631,O,0
2332,that,IN,VBD,noted,O,0.894,O,0
2333,because,IN,IN,that,O,0.146,O,0
2334,of,IN,IN,because,O,0.639,O,0
2335,rural,JJ,IN,of,O,0.798,O,0
2336,domination,NN,JJ,rural,O,0.312,O,0
2337,",",",",NN,domination,O,0,O,0
2338,"""",LQU,",",",",O,0,O,0
2339,A,DT,LQU,"""",O,0,O,3
2340,minority,NN,DT,A,O,0.59,O,0
2341,of,IN,NN,minority,O,0.639,O,0
2342,about,IN,IN,of,O,0.056,O,0
2343,25,CD,IN,about,O,0.033,O,0
2344,per,IN,CD,25,O,0.677,O,0
2345,cent,NN,IN,per,O,0.201,O,0
2346,of,IN,NN,cent,O,0.639,O,0
2347,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
2348,total,JJ,DT,the,O,0.914,O,0
2349,state,NN,JJ,total,O,0.857,O,0
2350,population,NN,NN,state,O,0.7,O,0
2351,is,VBZ,NN,population,O,0.502,O,0
2352,in,IN,VBZ,is,O,0.472,O,0
2353,majority,NN,IN,in,O,0.557,O,0
2354,control,NN,NN,majority,O,0.252,O,0
2355,of,IN,NN,control,O,0.639,O,0
2356,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
2357,Alabama,NNP,DT,the,I-ORG,0.083,O,1
2358,legislature,NN,NNP,Alabama,I-ORG,0.534,I-ORG,0
2359,.,.,NN,legislature,O,0,I-ORG,0
2360,"""",RQU,.,.,"O
These",0,O,0
2361,factors,NNS,RQU,"""",O,0.366,"O
These",0
2362,created,VBD,NNS,factors,O,0.267,O,0
2363,a,DT,VBD,created,O,0,O,0
2364,longstanding,JJ,DT,a,O,0.548,O,0
2365,tradition,NN,JJ,longstanding,O,0.917,O,0
2366,that,IN,NN,tradition,O,0.894,O,0
2367,any,DT,IN,that,O,0.11,O,0
2368,candidate,NN,DT,any,O,0.191,O,0
2369,who,WP,NN,candidate,O,0.974,O,0
2370,wanted,VBD,WP,who,O,0.956,O,0
2371,to,TO,VBD,wanted,O,0.911,O,0
2372,be,VB,TO,to,O,0.143,O,0
2373,viable,JJ,VB,be,O,0.946,O,0
2374,with,IN,JJ,viable,O,0.98,O,0
2375,white,JJ,IN,with,O,0.973,O,0
2376,voters,NNS,JJ,white,O,0.952,O,0
2377,had,VBD,NNS,voters,O,0.431,O,0
2378,to,TO,VBD,had,O,0.911,O,0
2379,run,VB,TO,to,O,0.797,O,0
2380,as,IN,VB,run,O,0.12,O,0
2381,a,DT,IN,as,O,0,O,0
2382,Democrat,NNP,DT,a,I-ORG,0.291,O,1
2383,regardless,RB,NNP,Democrat,O,0.76,I-ORG,0
2384,of,IN,RB,regardless,O,0.639,O,0
2385,political,JJ,IN,of,O,0.696,O,0
2386,beliefs,NNS,JJ,political,O,0.151,O,0
2387,.,.,NNS,beliefs,"O
Industrial",0,O,0
2388,development,NN,.,.,O,0.3,"O
Industrial",0
2389,related,VBN,NN,development,O,0.764,O,0
2390,to,TO,VBN,related,O,0.911,O,0
2391,the,DT,TO,to,O,0.895,O,0
2392,demands,NNS,DT,the,O,0.29,O,0
2393,of,IN,NNS,demands,O,0.639,O,0
2394,World,NNP,IN,of,I-MISC,0.989,O,1
2395,War,NNP,NNP,World,I-MISC,0.957,I-MISC,1
2396,II,NNP,NNP,War,I-MISC,0.467,I-MISC,3
2397,brought,VBD,NNP,II,O,0.178,I-MISC,0
2398,prosperity,NN,VBD,brought,O,0.729,O,0
2399,.,.,NN,prosperity,"O
In",0,O,0
2400,the,DT,.,.,O,0.895,"O
In",0
2401,1960s,NNS,DT,the,O,0.021,O,0
2402,under,IN,NNS,1960s,O,0.931,O,0
2403,Governor,NNP,IN,under,O,0.42,O,1
2404,George,NNP,NNP,Governor,I-PER,0.411,O,1
2405,Wallace,NNP,NNP,George,I-PER,0.955,I-PER,1
2406,",",",",NNP,Wallace,O,0,I-PER,0
2407,many,JJ,",",",",O,0.56,O,0
2408,whites,NNS,JJ,many,O,0.973,O,0
2409,in,IN,NNS,whites,O,0.472,O,0
2410,the,DT,IN,in,O,0.895,O,0
2411,state,NN,DT,the,O,0.857,O,0
2412,opposed,VBD,NN,state,O,0.649,O,0
2413,integration,NN,VBD,opposed,O,0.493,O,0
2414,efforts,NNS,NN,integration,O,0.329,O,0
2415,.,.,NNS,efforts,"O
After",0,O,0
2416,1972,CD,.,.,O,0.022,"O
After",0
2417,",",",",CD,1972,O,0,O,0
2418,the,DT,",",",",O,0.895,O,0
2419,state,NN,DT,the,O,0.857,O,0
2420,'s,POS,NN,state,O,0,O,0
2421,white,JJ,POS,'s,O,0.973,O,0
2422,voters,NNS,JJ,white,O,0.952,O,0
2423,shifted,VBD,NNS,voters,O,0.826,O,0
2424,much,RB,VBD,shifted,O,0.606,O,0
2425,of,IN,RB,much,O,0.639,O,0
2426,their,PRP$,IN,of,O,0.896,O,0
2427,support,NN,PRP$,their,O,0.877,O,0
2428,to,TO,NN,support,O,0.911,O,0
2429,Republican,NNP,TO,to,I-MISC,0.771,O,1
2430,candidates,NNS,NNP,Republican,O,0.191,I-MISC,0
2431,in,IN,NNS,candidates,O,0.472,O,0
2432,presidential,JJ,IN,in,O,0.714,O,0
2433,elections,NNS,JJ,presidential,O,0.334,O,0
2434,(,LRB,NNS,elections,O,0,O,0
2435,as,IN,LRB,(,O,0.12,O,0
2436,also,RB,IN,as,O,0.092,O,0
2437,occurred,VBD,RB,also,O,0.638,O,0
2438,in,IN,VBD,occurred,O,0.472,O,0
2439,neighboring,VBG,IN,in,O,0.618,O,0
2440,southern,JJ,VBG,neighboring,O,0.847,O,0
2441,states,NNS,JJ,southern,O,0.858,O,0
2442,),RRB,NNS,states,O,0,O,0
2443,.,.,RRB,),"O
Since",0,O,0
2444,1990,CD,.,.,O,0.024,"O
Since",0
2445,the,DT,CD,1990,O,0.895,O,0
2446,majority,NN,DT,the,O,0.557,O,0
2447,of,IN,NN,majority,O,0.639,O,0
2448,whites,NNS,IN,of,O,0.973,O,0
2449,in,IN,NNS,whites,O,0.472,O,0
2450,the,DT,IN,in,O,0.895,O,0
2451,state,NN,DT,the,O,0.857,O,0
2452,have,VBP,NN,state,O,0.437,O,0
2453,voted,VBN,VBP,have,O,0.951,O,0
2454,increasingly,RB,VBN,voted,O,0.476,O,0
2455,Republican,JJ,RB,increasingly,I-MISC,0.771,O,1
2456,in,IN,JJ,Republican,O,0.472,I-MISC,0
2457,state,NN,IN,in,O,0.857,O,0
2458,elections,NNS,NN,state,O,0.334,O,0
2459,.,.,NNS,elections,"O
Democrats",0,O,0
2460,are,VBP,.,.,O,0.115,"O
Democrats",0
2461,still,RB,VBP,are,O,0.861,O,0
2462,the,DT,RB,still,O,0.895,O,0
2463,majority,NN,DT,the,O,0.557,O,0
2464,party,NN,NN,majority,O,0.671,O,0
2465,in,IN,NN,party,O,0.472,O,0
2466,both,DT,IN,in,O,0.171,O,0
2467,houses,NNS,DT,both,O,0.462,O,0
2468,of,IN,NNS,houses,O,0.639,O,0
2469,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
2470,legislature,NN,DT,the,O,0.534,O,0
2471,.,.,NN,legislature,"O
Alabama",0,O,0
2548,has,VBZ,.,.,O,0.436,"O
Alabama",0
2549,coastline,VBN,VBZ,has,O,0.224,O,0
2550,at,IN,VBN,coastline,O,0.125,O,0
2551,the,DT,IN,at,O,0.895,O,0
2552,Gulf,NNP,DT,the,I-LOC,0.429,O,1
2553,of,IN,NNP,Gulf,I-LOC,0.639,I-LOC,0
2554,Mexico,NNP,IN,of,I-LOC,0.58,I-LOC,1
2555,",",",",NNP,Mexico,O,0,I-LOC,0
2556,in,IN,",",",",O,0.472,O,0
2557,the,DT,IN,in,O,0.895,O,0
2558,extreme,JJ,DT,the,O,0.365,O,0
2559,southern,JJ,JJ,extreme,O,0.847,O,0
2560,edge,NN,JJ,southern,O,0.324,O,0
2561,of,IN,NN,edge,O,0.639,O,0
2562,the,DT,IN,of,O,0.895,O,0
2563,state,NN,DT,the,O,0.857,O,0
2564,.,.,NN,state,"O
Alabama",0,O,0
2565,ranges,NNS,.,.,O,0.742,"O
Alabama",0
2566,in,IN,NNS,ranges,O,0.472,O,0
2567,elevation,NN,IN,in,O,0.335,O,0
2568,from,IN,NN,elevation,O,0.403,O,0
2569,sea,NN,IN,from,O,0.808,O,0
2570,level,NN,NN,sea,O,0.537,O,0
2571,at,IN,NN,level,O,0.125,O,0
2572,Mobile,NNP,IN,at,I-LOC,0.593,O,1
2573,Bay,NNP,NNP,Mobile,I-LOC,0.142,I-LOC,1
2574,to,TO,NNP,Bay,O,0.911,I-LOC,0
2575,over,IN,TO,to,O,0.659,O,0
2576,"1,800",CD,IN,over,O,0,O,0
2577,feet,NNS,CD,"1,800",O,0.374,O,0
2578,(,LRB,NNS,feet,O,0,O,0
2579,550,CD,LRB,(,O,0.043,O,0
2580,m,NN,CD,550,O,0,O,0
2581,),RRB,NN,m,O,0,O,0
2582,in,IN,RRB,),O,0.472,O,0
2583,the,DT,IN,in,O,0.895,O,0
2584,Appalachian,JJ,DT,the,I-LOC,0.112,O,1
2585,Mountains,NNS,JJ,Appalachian,I-LOC,0.603,I-LOC,1
2586,in,IN,NNS,Mountains,O,0.472,I-LOC,0
2587,the,DT,IN,in,O,0.895,O,0
2588,northeast,NN,DT,the,O,0.627,O,0
2589,.,.,NN,northeast,"O
The",0,O,0
2590,highest,JJS,.,.,O,0.45,"O
The",0
2591,point,NN,JJS,highest,O,0.694,O,0
2592,is,VBZ,NN,point,O,0.502,O,0
2593,Mount,NNP,VBZ,is,I-LOC,0.602,O,1
2594,Cheaha,NNP,NNP,Mount,I-LOC,0.21,I-LOC,1
2595,",",",",NNP,Cheaha,O,0,I-LOC,0
2596,at,IN,",",",",O,0.125,O,0
2597,a,DT,IN,at,O,0,O,0
2598,height,NN,DT,a,O,0.444,O,0
2599,of,IN,NN,height,O,0.639,O,0
2600,2407,CD,IN,of,O,0.033,O,0
2601,ft,NN,CD,2407,O,0.405,O,0
2602,(,LRB,NN,ft,O,0,O,0
2603,734,CD,LRB,(,O,0.049,O,0
2604,m,NN,CD,734,O,0,O,0
2605,),RRB,NN,m,O,0,O,0
2606,.,.,RRB,),"O
Ala.",0,O,0
2607,'s,POS,.,.,O,0,"O
Ala.",0
2608,land,NN,POS,'s,O,0.522,O,0
2609,consists,VBZ,NN,land,O,0.247,O,0
2610,of,IN,VBZ,consists,O,0.639,O,0
2611,22,CD,IN,of,O,0.032,O,0
2612,million,CD,CD,22,O,0.587,O,0
2613,acres,NNS,CD,million,O,0.063,O,0
2614,(,LRB,NNS,acres,O,0,O,0
2615,89000,CD,LRB,(,O,0.053,O,0
2616,km,NN,CD,89000,O,0.516,O,0
2617,2,CD,NN,km,O,0,O,0
2618,),RRB,CD,2,O,0,O,0
2619,of,IN,RRB,),O,0.639,O,0
2620,forest,NN,IN,of,O,0.39,O,0
2621,or,CC,NN,forest,O,0.651,O,0
2622,67,CD,CC,or,O,0.048,O,0
2623,%,NN,CD,67,O,0,O,0
2624,of,IN,NN,%,O,0.639,O,0
2625,total,JJ,IN,of,O,0.914,O,0
2626,land,NN,JJ,total,O,0.522,O,0
2627,area,NN,NN,land,O,0.115,O,0
2628,.,.,NN,area,"O
Areas",0,O,0
2629,in,IN,.,.,O,0.472,"O
Areas",0
2630,Alabama,NNP,IN,in,I-LOC,0.083,O,1
2631,administered,VBN,NNP,Alabama,O,0.071,I-LOC,0
2632,by,IN,VBN,administered,O,0.185,O,0
2633,the,DT,IN,by,O,0.895,O,0
2634,National,NNP,DT,the,I-ORG,0.614,O,1
2635,Park,NNP,NNP,National,I-ORG,0.666,I-ORG,1
2636,Service,NNP,NNP,Park,I-ORG,0.817,I-ORG,1
2637,include,VBP,NNP,Service,O,0.473,I-ORG,0
2638,Horseshoe,NNP,VBP,include,I-LOC,0.459,O,1
2639,Bend,NNP,NNP,Horseshoe,I-LOC,0.155,I-LOC,1
2640,National,NNP,NNP,Bend,I-LOC,0.614,I-LOC,1
2641,Military,NNP,NNP,National,I-LOC,0.585,I-LOC,1
2642,Park,NNP,NNP,Military,I-LOC,0.666,I-LOC,1
2643,near,IN,NNP,Park,O,0.616,I-LOC,0
2644,Alexander,NNP,IN,near,I-LOC,0.086,O,1
2645,City,NNP,NNP,Alexander,I-LOC,0.217,I-LOC,1
2646,;,;,NNP,City,O,0,I-LOC,0
2647,Little,NNP,;,;,I-LOC,0.544,O,1
2648,River,NNP,NNP,Little,I-LOC,0.79,I-LOC,1
2649,Canyon,NNP,NNP,River,I-LOC,0.192,I-LOC,1
2650,National,NNP,NNP,Canyon,I-LOC,0.614,I-LOC,1
2651,Preserve,NNP,NNP,National,I-LOC,0.713,I-LOC,1
2652,near,IN,NNP,Preserve,O,0.616,I-LOC,0
2653,Fort,NNP,IN,near,I-LOC,0.394,O,1
2654,Payne,NNP,NNP,Fort,I-LOC,0.673,I-LOC,1
2655,;,;,NNP,Payne,O,0,I-LOC,0
2656,Russell,NNP,;,;,I-LOC,0.799,O,1
2657,Cave,NNP,NNP,Russell,I-LOC,0.2,I-LOC,1
2658,National,NNP,NNP,Cave,I-LOC,0.614,I-LOC,1
2659,Monument,NNP,NNP,National,I-LOC,0.597,I-LOC,1
2660,in,IN,NNP,Monument,O,0.472,I-LOC,0
2661,Bridgeport,NNP,IN,in,I-LOC,0.174,O,1
2662,;,;,NNP,Bridgeport,O,0,I-LOC,0
2663,Tuskegee,NNP,;,;,I-LOC,0.928,O,1
2664,Airmen,NNP,NNP,Tuskegee,I-LOC,0.08,I-LOC,1
2665,National,NNP,NNP,Airmen,I-LOC,0.614,I-LOC,1
2666,Historic,NNP,NNP,National,I-LOC,0.454,I-LOC,1
2667,Site,NNP,NNP,Historic,I-LOC,0.832,I-LOC,1
2668,in,IN,NNP,Site,O,0.472,I-LOC,0
2669,Tuskegee,NNP,IN,in,I-LOC,0.928,O,1
2670,;,;,NNP,Tuskegee,O,0,I-LOC,0
2671,and,CC,;,;,O,0.104,O,0
2672,Tuskegee,NNP,CC,and,I-ORG,0.928,O,1
2673,Institute,NNP,NNP,Tuskegee,I-ORG,0.49,I-ORG,1
2674,National,NNP,NNP,Institute,I-ORG,0.614,I-ORG,1
2675,Historic,NNP,NNP,National,I-ORG,0.454,I-ORG,1
2676,Site,NNP,NNP,Historic,I-ORG,0.832,I-ORG,1
2677,near,IN,NNP,Site,O,0.616,I-ORG,0
2678,Tuskegee,NNP,IN,near,I-LOC,0.928,O,1
2679,.,.,NNP,Tuskegee,"O
A",0,I-LOC,0
2680,notable,JJ,.,.,O,0.63,"O
A",0
2681,natural,JJ,JJ,notable,O,0.615,O,0
2682,wonder,NN,JJ,natural,O,0.985,O,0
2683,in,IN,NN,wonder,O,0.472,O,0
2684,Alabama,NNP,IN,in,I-LOC,0.083,O,1
2685,is,VBZ,NNP,Alabama,O,0.502,I-LOC,0
2686,"""",LQU,VBZ,is,I-LOC,0,O,0
2687,Natural,NNP,LQU,"""",I-LOC,0.615,I-LOC,1
2688,Bridge,NNP,NNP,Natural,I-LOC,0.174,I-LOC,1
